阻击电话亭
据估计纽约五个行政区 人口约有八百万人
There are an estimated 8 million people in the five boroughs of New York.
整个大都会区 人口为一千两百万
1 2 million in the greater metropolitan area.
使用的电话线路 约为一千万
There are almost 1 0 million telephone exchange lines.
电话公司超过五十家
Over 50 phone services.
三百万名纽约人 持有移动电话
3 million New Yorkers are cell phone users.
看到人们自言自语 以前我们会觉得他们疯了
It used to be a mark of insanity to see people talk to themselves.
现在那是地位的象征 移动电话快速取代了公共电话
Now it's a mark of status. And speed dial is quickly replacing the drop of a coin.
虽然有越来越多的人 使用移动电话...
Despite increased usage of cellular devices...
据估计有四百五十万居民 及两百万的观光客...
...an estimated 4.5 million residents and 2 million visitors...
仍利用公共电话 因应日常生活所需
...still utilize pay phones on a regular basis.
这是位于五十三街 跟第八街路口的公共电话亭...
This is the telephone booth at 53rd and 8th...
或许它是曼哈顿西区 最后一个公共电话亭
...perhaps the last vestige of privacy on Manhattan 's West Side.
它是同类型的电话亭当中 唯一还在使用的
It is the last booth of its type, still in regular operation.
每天最多有三百通电话从此地拨出
Up to 300 calls daily originate here.
过去六个月来 这里被偷了四十一次
This location has been burglarized 4 1 times in the last six months.
威瑞森排定了日期 要拆除掉这个电话亭...
Verizon has scheduled this structure to be torn down...
在明天早上八点 此地将会出现一座新报摊
...and replaced with a kiosk as of 8 a.m. tomorrow.
在还不到两个街区远处...
Hardly two blocks away...
最后一个使用这个电话亭的人 就在这里
...meet the man who is to be the final occupant of that booth.
唐尼  听我说
Donny. Donny. Donny, listen to me.
我说我会让你上杂志封面 我正在做安排
I said I'd get you magazine coverage, and I'm getting you in a magazine.
听着  你要相信我 这些人的不要就是要
Look, you gotta trust me. No means yes to these people.
帮我联络 流行杂志
Get What's Up? magazine on the line.
是的  我知道了
Yeah, I heard you.
唐尼  我已经接通了 流行杂志
Donny, I got What's Up? magazine on the line.
他们想多了解你 所以我要挂了
They wanna know about you, so I'm hanging up.
她叫艾莉卡还是拉儿丝 我真的分不出来
This is Erica or Lars. I can't tell the difference.
-我是史都 -我们说过不行了
-You got Stu. -We said no.
我没有听见 所以我要再给你一次机会
I didn't hear you, so I'm giving you a second chance.
-我们是不碰魔术师的 -魔术师?
-We don't do magicians. -Magicians?.
唐尼是个艺术家 他长得就跟超级名模一样
Donny G is an artist who happens to look like a supermodel.
-新好男人邀请他上封面 -新好男人要他?
-The New Guys is offering him the cover. -New Guys wants him?.
我还没有告诉我的客户 我最喜欢的客户...
And I haven't told my client, my favorite client...
我要打这通电话  好吗? 他要新好男人
...that I am making this call, all right?. He wants New Guys.
我要你们 我可以说服他答应...
I want you and I can make him come around...
但如果下班前你不给我答案 你会失去这次机会
...but you'll lose us if I don't hear from you by end of business.
联络新好男人 告诉他流行杂志要给我们封面
Get New Guys. T ell him What's Up? is offering a cover.
好的  大Q
Okay. Big Q.
亚当  我知道有三个人在找人溜狗 这是你的大好机会
Adam, I know three people looking for dog walkers. That could be you.
"坐下  别动  别担心  毛毛 我会帮你清理大便跟擦屁股"
"Sit. Stay. Don't worry, Fluffy, I'll clean your shit and wipe your ass."
-我是史都 -我的派对怎么了?史都
-You got Stu. -What's up with my party, Stu?.
我刚告诉我的助理 打通电话...
I was just telling my assistant to get my favorite client...
给我最喜欢的客户 结果你就来了  大美人
...on the phone, and here you are. Nice.
听好  我们要再找时间 帮你办首映派对
Listen. Seriously, we gotta look at a new night for your release party.
两场首映会及一场募款会撞期 所有的场地都被订走了
There are two premieres, a fundraiser. All the happening places are booked.
如果我们更改日期--
If we move the date--
少来这套  混蛋 我大Q是不会听你摆布的
Voodoo on you-do, motherfucker, from Big Q to Big Stu!
-大Q  你要讲道理 -混蛋  我是黑社会大哥
-Big Q, be reasonable. -Motherfucker, I'm a gangster!
-我不必讲道理 -讯号不太清楚  喂?大Q
-I don't gotta be reasonable! -You're cutting out.
如果你敢再那样跟我说话 下一次我会杀了你这个混蛋
Next time I'm gonna kill your cracker-ass if you keep talking about me like that!
对吧?
Right?.
纽约警察在十一点钟方向
N.Y.P.D. Blue, 1 1 o'clock.
史杜利  最辛苦的宣传人员 你的生意还好吗?
Stuey, the hardest working PR guy. How's business?.
我得告诉你多少次?伟特 我是公关人员
How many times I have to tell you, Wyatt?. I'm a publicist.
-您的门票 -没错
-Tickets. -Tickets.
四张布兰妮的门票  对吧?
Four for Britney Spears, right?.
你在演艺界真的能呼风唤雨 史杜利
You put the " Ho" in show business, Stuey.
我是史都  情况如何?
It's Stu. What do you got for me?.
他们刚刚安排夏普太太 再度住进贝利维尔
They just checked Mrs. Sharp into Bellevue again.
-联络第六页  告诉布兰妮我爱她 -好的
-Page Six. Tell Britney I send my love. -All right.
好好享受吧
Enjoy the show.
等一下  第六页杂志  我是拉娜
Hold on a sec. Page Six, this is Lana.
保佑你  拉娜  我是史都薛帕德 保佑你
Bless you. Lana, it's Stu Shepard. Bless you.
-是你还是你老板要找我? -我要找你
-ls it you or your boss calling?. -It's me.
我想找一些 跟我想法一样的人
I'm looking for some mutual back-scratching.
你拿到了纽约警方的资料 我要你帮我的忙
You get my privileged N.Y.P.D. Blue info and I get you to save my ass.
现在不行  史都  我生病了
Not now, Stu. I'm a sick woman.
这会让你觉得 好过一点
This is going to make you feel better.
赢得东尼奖的制片杰佛瑞夏普 把他太太送回到戒毒中心
Tony-winning producer Jeffrey Sharp tossed his wife back into drug rehab.
好吧 你到底想做什么?
Nice. What do you want for that little tidbit?.
你最好对我好一点 不然我不会接你电话
You better be nice to me while I'm on the way up and taking your calls.
猴子爬得越高 你越容易看到他的屁股
The higher the monkey climbs, the more you see of his ass.
好心一点  拉娜
Have a heart, Lana.
今天我那个白痴助理 把我的大客户资料传真给你
Listen, today my half-wit assistant faxed you regarding my favorite client.
她是个很棒的歌手 打算转型当演员
Great singer, about to turn great actress.
-又是一个大波霸? -听着  我在讲电话  不能提名字
-Another little Miss Tits and Ass?. -Look, I'm on cell, no names.
那是我们办公室的最高机密 你没把它登出去吧?
That was strictly in-office information. You didn't print it, did you?.
-我知道了 -好吧  告诉我理查还没看到它
-I got it. -All right, tell me Richard didn't see it.
他没写在他的专栏里吗?
He didn't put it in the column?.
史都在线上 他害怕自己会丢掉工作
Stu's on the phone, scared he's gonna lose his job.
他的助理误传了资料来给你 他想把它要回去
His office sent you something by mistake. He wants it.
叫他别做梦了 立刻把它登在专栏的最上方
You tell him T.F.B. Put that at the top of the column.
-史都  已经登出去了  抱歉 -是吗?
-Stu, it ran, sorry. -Yeah?.
-天啊  不 -我真的很抱歉
-Oh, God. Oh, no. -I'm really sorry.
太棒了
Yes!
流行杂志把唐尼的照片 放在"最新流行情报"
What's Up? magazine offered Donny G a photo in "What's Hot and Happening."
-天杀的  叫他们去死 -他在开会
-Fuck them. Make them sweat. -He's on a conference call.
他还得讲上一阵子  是的 要他回电吗?好的  再见
He could take a while. Yeah, can he call you back?. Okay. All right, bye.
-十分顺利 -谢谢你
-Pretty smooth. -Thank you.
如果你能融会贯通 我教你的一切...
If you can absorb everything I teach you...
集中注意力  买些新衣服 你可以在公关界大红特红
...focus and get a new wardrobe, you can make it big in public relations.
-我感觉得到 -太酷了
-I got a sense. -Cool. Cool. Cool.
-你还好吗? -你好
-Up, T?. -How you doing, man?.
是马利欧
Mario's!
嘿!别逃  史都!
Hey! Hey! Hey! Not so fast, Stu!
你为什么每次经过我的办公室 都会拔腿就跑?
How come you run every time you go past my place, huh?.
-因为我很忙  马利欧 -是吗?
-Because I'm busy, Mario. -Yeah?.
喔  你休想再白吃白喝了  好吗?
Well, no more drinks or free meals, okay?.
你以为在邮报上帮我登个小专访 就能白吃白喝六个月?别做梦
One lousy mention in the Post, you expect to eat for six months?. No!
马利欧  或许我能安排 在你的餐厅举办本月最辣的派对
Mario, maybe I could throw the hippest party this month your way.
-史都 -不行  我的客户会杀了我
-Stu. -No, I couldn't. My clients would kill me.
-什么派对? -新生代饶舌歌手大Q要办派对
-What hip party?. -It's just Big Q, the hottest new rap star.
-当地电视台会来做转播.... -第九频道跟十一频道
-There'll be local TV coverage.... -Nine and 1 1.
MTV音乐台  BET台跟VH1台
MTV, BET, VH1.
但我答应了其他客人 他们会付钱给我
But I promised other clients, people who actually pay me.
-不  你欠我钱 -日期一定得是十八号晚上
-No, you owe me. -It's gotta be the night of the 1 8th.
准备八十人份的自助餐 唱片公司会准备酒...
Toss in a buffet for 80 people, record company will pick up the booze...
我会介绍你认识很多名人
...and I will deliver you celebrities.
你有什么条件我都答应  好吗?
Anything you want, okay?.
多加点菜色 把壁纸换新  整修一下洗手间
Expand the menu, wallpaper those bathrooms, for God's sake.
要认识那些名人 可没那么容易
You only get one shot with celebrities.
谢谢你  史都
Thank you. Thank you, Stu!
-那一招真的是太高明了 -听我说
-That was fucking brilliant. -Listen.
打电话告诉大Q 我们帮他订到城里最酷的场地
Call Big Q. Tell him we got him the hippest place in town on his date.
-通知流行杂志 -是的
-Call What's Up? -Yeah.
我们愿意接受他们的条件
We'll take their offer.
送一瓶威士忌 给第六页杂志的拉娜...
Messenger a bottle of Jameson's to Lana at Page Six...
-附上一张纸条--快记下来 -遵命
-...with a note saying-- Write this down. -Got it.
-把鸡汤给喝了吧  爱你的史都 -"把鸡汤给喝了吧  爱你的史都"
-lrish chicken soup. Love, Stu. -" lrish chicken soup. Love, Stu."
-好心一点总是能捞到好处 -没错
-All right, no harm being gracious. -Yeah.
好了  事实上最好的方法是 你亲自把它送过去
Okay. Actually, better off, deliver it over yourself.
-你就会有机会多认识一些人 -我会亲自送过去的
-Get to know the players. -I'll do that.
谢谢你愿意花时间教我
Thank you for teaching me.
-亚当  你没有西装吗? -我真的没有
-And, Adam, don't you have a suit?. -Actually, no.
拿去吧  去买套西装
Here. Get yourself one.
-我很快就会开始付你薪水 -那真的是太棒了
-I'm gonna start paying you soon. -Yeah, I hope so.
-有一大堆找你的留言 -我开会要来不及了  先搁着吧
-You got a bunch of messages. -I'm late for a meeting. Hold them.
-好的 -就这样
-All right. -All right.
-再见  史都 -再见  亚当
-See you, Stu! -See you, Adam!
城市饭店
-对不起 -我正在打电话
-Excuse me. -I'm trying to make a call here.
你的披萨来了  一半腊肠 一半蘑菇的特脆口味
This is for you. Half-pepperoni, half-mushroom, extra crisp.
你听说过有人会把披萨 外送到电话亭吗?
You ever heard of delivering a pizza to a phone booth?.
我没听过这种事
I don't think so.
把披萨送给在百老汇跟八街路口 的五十三街电话亭里打电话的男士
Gentleman occupying phone booth, 53rd, between Broadway and 8th.
你弄错了
It's a mistake.
你要我怎么处理这个披萨? 钱都已经付了
What am I supposed to do with the pie?. It's all paid for.
在街角那边 有一个流浪汉
There's a homeless guy around the block.
把披萨送给他并告诉他
Give him the pizza and say
"你可以离开  但这披萨跟定你了"
"You can turn away, but you can't make it go away."
他会以为我想毒死他 那些流浪汉最会乱想了
He'll think I'm trying to poison him. They always get that idea.
把那个该死的披萨拿开  好吗?
Get off the fucking pizza, all right?.
你不应该那么说的
That language is uncalled for.
我的老天爷
Holy shit!
对不起  请把它还给订披萨的人
I'm sorry. Please return to sender.
快滚开
Fuck off.
拿去吧  这是五块钱  把披萨吃掉
Here you go, $5. Eat the pizza yourself.
你看起来很需要好好地吃一顿
You look like you could use a good meal.
你好
Hello.
潘  你相信有个疯子 刚刚想外送披萨来给我吗?
Pam, could you believe some nut case just tried to deliver me a pizza?.
你为什么每天会在同一个时间 在相同的电话亭打电话给我?
Why are you always in the same phone booth, same time, every day?.
-你在休息  对吧? -谢天谢地  我们今天忙死了
-Well, it's quitting time, right?. -Thank God, we were mobbed today.
你今天还好吗?
So how's your day?.
现在觉得好多了 甜心
It's getting better by the minute, sweetheart.
今天你帮哪个最有名的明星 做宣传呢?
Who's the most famous person you publicized today?.
-就是你啊 -真的吗?
-You. -Really?.
我告诉几个专栏作家梅尔吉勃孙 在为他的新片寻找女主角
I told a few columnists Mel Gibson was looking for actresses for his film.
我说可能的人选包括了 卡麦蓉狄亚  茱莉亚萝伯兹...
And I said the possibilities were Cameron Diaz, Julia Roberts...
以及我最喜欢的客户  也就是你
...and my favorite client, you.
你真的不必那么做
You didn't really do that.
你希望被人注意 首先得常常让人听见你的名字
First step toward being noticed is being mentioned.
我刚刚到城市饭店 开完会出来
I just got out of a conference at the City Hotel.
我想或许你可以 赶过来
I was thinking you could come down.
我要介绍你认识一些人 我们可以一起喝几杯
There are a couple of people and a few martinis I'd like to introduce you to.
-史都  我-- -听我说  潘
-Stu, l-- -Listen, Pam. Pam. Pam.
我们应该好好谈谈 你的事业  快来吧
It's about time we talked about your career. Come on.
我真的很想去  但我答应过我同学 我会参加学校的彩排
I feel awful but I promised my scene partner that I would rehearse for class.
我们要演出征服情海的一场戏 我饰演薇妮齐薇格的角色
We're doing a scene from Jerry Maguire. I'm playing Renee Zellweger's part.
太棒了  听着  我调开 开会的时间是希望能跟你见面...
That's great. Look, I rescheduled a meeting to see you...
但我想我应该能把它调回来
...but I guess I can reschedule it back.
-你在生气吗? -别担心  我没有生气
-Are you mad?. -Don't worry about it. I'm not mad.
明天再说吧
Maybe tomorrow.
是啊  再见
Yeah, later.
-听我说  史都.... -什么事?
-Look, Stu.... -What?.
我爱你
Big kiss.
我也是
You too.
-你好 -这真的是太有趣了
-Yeah. -Isn't it funny?
你听到电话铃声 那可能是其他人的电话...
You hear a phone ring, and it could be anybody...
但电话铃声一响 你会很自然地去接起它  对吧?
...but a ringing phone has to be answered, doesn 't it?
什么?
What?.
我希望你了解 你让我有多伤心
I hope you realize how you've hurt my feelings.
-你到底是谁? -别想挂电话
-Who the fuck is this?. -Don't think about leaving that phone.
-你打错电话了  老哥 -那个披萨非常好吃
-Wrong number, pal. -It was a perfectly delicious pizza.
你真的会很后悔 自己没有收下它
You're certainly going to wish you had accepted it.
你一定是在开玩笑 关于披萨的事  那真的很有趣
Naturally, this is part of the gag. The pizza bit. That was funny shit.
我本来要送披萨给你 让你有力气应付接下来的事
Well, its purpose was to keep your strength up for what's coming next.
-接下来我会把电话挂掉 -不  你不会那么做的
-What's coming next is I'm hanging up. -Oh, no, you won 't.
-你得学会服从我 -服从你?
- You're going to learn to obey me. -Obey you?.
-你到底是谁? -我只是一个喜欢看着你的人
-Who is this?. -Someone who enjoys watching you.
看着我?
Watching me?.
对  我喜欢你今天的穿着 蓝黑色的西装  非常具意大利风味
Yes, I love the suit you're wearing today. Black on raspberry sorbet. Very Italian.
你--?你在哪里?
Where--?. Where are you?.
这里有好几百扇窗户 你为什么不自己来找找看呢?
There are hundreds of windows out there. Why don 't you check them out?
-我现在在做什么? -你在抓头
-So, what am I doing now?. - You're scratching your head.
现在你把头发往后梳
Now you're brushing your hair back.
那么做太不智了  史都
That's not very nice, Stu.
你叫我史都?
Did you call me Stu?.
-谁是史都?我不认识叫史都的人 -怎么?你要我叫你史都华吗?
-Who' s Stu?. I don' t know any Stu. -Why, do you prefer Stuart?
在这个地区 很多人都认识我
A lot of people in this neighborhood know me.
史都华薛帕德  家住西五十一街 1326号三楼前座
Stuart Shepard, 1 326 West 5 1st Street, Third Floor, front.
-去找其他人开玩笑吧  老兄 -我也知道潘蜜拉麦费登的事
-Go mind-fuck some other guy, pal. -I know Pamela McFadden too.
挂断电话 对你没有任何一点好处
It's not in your best interest to disconnect me.
可能有人会因此受伤
Someone could get hurt.
怎么了?史都
What's the matter, Stu?
如果你是连我都无法捧红的 超级烂演员...
If you' re some fucked-up, failed actor I wouldn' t handle...
或是被我开除的助理 我一定会逮到你并且毁了你
...or some prick intern I fired, I will hunt you down and I will crush you.
你将永远无法在这个城市工作
You will never work in this town.
我有办法把人捧成神
I can turn people into gods...
就算你现在还没被毁掉 我也能把你逼得走投无路
...and I can turn you into a total fucking loser if you weren't one already.
你听到了吗? 我惹毛你了吗?喂
Do you hear me?. Am I upsetting you?. Hello.
喔  你以为我想做什么? 你以为我是来报复你的吗?
Oh, you think I'm gonna, what?. Pay you off or something?.
-告诉我你到底想做什么 -现在你想跟我说话了
-T ell me what you want. -Now you want to talk to me.
是我的助理亚当 唆使你这么做的吗?
Did Adam at my office put you up to this?.
不  这完全是我一个人的主意
No, I thought this up all by myself.
随便你  我要挂电话了
Keep thinking. I'm hanging up.
我会帮你跟你太太凯莉打招呼 待会再联络
I'll say hi to your wife, Kelly, for you. Talk to you later.
搞什么--?
What the--?.
现在无法执行 回拨功能--
The callback feature cannot be activated--
混蛋
Motherfucker.
-告诉我你到底想做什么 -我要你专心听我说
-T ell me what you want. -I want your complete attention.
-你是演员吗? -没错  我是你没捧红的演员
-Are you an actor?. - Yes. One of your pathetic failed ones.
-红不起来真的是让人很难过 -你说的对
-lt' s tough when you' re not known. - Tell me about it.
你不必费力找我把我毁了 反正我在这里也找不到工作
You don 't have to hunt me and crush me. I can't get work in this town as it is.
我在百老汇及曼哈顿演过 一些小角色  但现在我失业了
I've done some off-Broadway, some off-Manhattan plays, but that dried up.
所以我做服务生跟清洁工 赚些小钱来付房租
Now I wait tables, clean toilets, anything to make the rent.
现在我成了一个大笑话
I'm a walking cliche.
我可以帮你 安排试镜的机会
I can help you. I can get you auditions.
试镜?你不是经纪人 你是搞公关的
Auditions? You're not an agent. You're a publicist.
对  但我有关系 我认识经纪人  我能帮你安排
Yeah, but I have contacts. I know agents. I can get you an audition.
-真的吗? -没错
-Really? -Yeah.
喔  我希望 你能打电话给某人
Well, there is someone I'd like you to call.
是谁
Name it.
试试你踏进电话亭后 第一个拨出的电话号码
Try the number you dialed when you first got into the booth.
-我不知道你在说什么 -真的吗?
-I don't know what you're talking about. -No?
那么你的运气不错 因为我把它记下来了
Lucky you then, because I wrote it down.
我看得到你拨了哪些号码 快来看看潘是不是还在工作
I can see every number you pressed. Let's see if Pam is still at work.
-不 -看来我得亲自打电话给她
-No. -Then I guess I'll have to do it.
-听着  千万别那么做 -太迟了  电话已经接通
-Look, don' t! -Too late. It's already ringing.
-我会接上扩音器以便你听见对话 -别开玩笑
-I'll put her on speaker so you can hear. -You' re fucking kidding me.
史都  我从不开玩笑
Stu, I never kid.
-喂 -喂  潘
-Hello. - Well, hello, Pam.
-你好  哪位? -我是史都的好朋友
-Hi, who' s this?. -It's a good friend of Stu's.
-他没有多少好朋友 -你认识史都?
-And he hasn 't got many. -You know Stu?.
我知道他在说谎
I know he lies.
-你是谁? -别担心
-Who is this?. -Don 't worry about that.
史都正在听我们说话 他听得到我们所有的对话
Stu's listening in. He can hear what we 're saying about him.
-史都  真的吗?你也在吗? -潘  快把电话挂掉
-Stu, is that true?. Are you there?. -Pam, hang up the goddamn phone!
她听不到你说话  史都
She can 't hear you, Stu.
潘  恐怕史都并没有 完全对你坦白
Pam, I'm afraid Stu hasn 't been totally honest with you.
-你是什么意思? -别这么做
-What do you mean?. -Don' t do this.
-史都一直在骗你 -潘  快挂掉电话
-Stu has been lying to you. -Pam, hang up.
为什么 一个有移动电话的人...
Now, why would a man who has a cell phone...
每天都要从电话亭 打电话给你
...call you every day from a phone booth?
-他说那样子比较安静 -潘  那真的是太蠢了
-Because he said it' s quiet. -Pam, that's just stupid.
那是因为他太太 会检查他的移动电话帐单
It's because his wife checks his cell phone bills.
-那样就不会有你的电话记录 -我的天啊
-No record of his calls to you. -Jesus Christ.
-他说他未婚 -他已经结婚了
-He said he wasn't married. -Oh, he 's married.
他太太叫做凯莉  我从没见过她 但她的声音很好听
Her name is Kelly. I've never seen her but she sounds lovely.
你觉得他为什么 要邀请你到城市饭店?
Why do you think he invites you to the City Hotel?
-低俗的女孩只适合到廉价的饭店 -混蛋
-Cheap rooms for cheap girls. -Asshole.
他说他要捧红你 那样子你就会跟他上床
He 's telling you all this so you'll sleep with him.
-他在说谎  潘  别听他的 -我知道  好吗?
-He' s lying, Pam. Don' t listen. -I know that, okay?.
虽然我来自蒙大拿州 但那里也有男人
I may be from Montana, but we have men there also.
我并没有计划 要跟他上床
I wasn' t planning on sleeping with him.
只是现在 我在这里认识的人不多
I just don't know a lot of people here right now.
他长得很帅 还说他会帮我
And he's cute and he said that he would help me.
-你从来没问过我的婚姻状况 -他从来没有捧红过任何人  再见
-You never asked me if I was married. -He's never made anyone a star. Bye.
喂
Hello?.
现在轮到你了  史都
Back to you, Stu.
我得趁下个混蛋占便宜之前 阻止一场闹剧
Gotta hit this trick before the next bitch takes my score.
-快滚开 -滚开?把电话挂掉  混蛋
-Go away. -Go away?. Hang up the phone, nigga.
大混蛋 居然还瞪我  死王八
This motherfucker, you don't eyeball me. Bitch.
你为什么要这么做? 我伤害过你吗?我--
Why are you doing this?. Did I ever harm you?. Did l--?.
-我们现在得打电话给凯莉 -她不在家
-Now, let's call Kelly. -She's not home.
但我相信 她应该在哥伦布的店里
Oh, but I'm sure she 's at the shop on Columbus.
你怎么会知道这些事?
How the fuck do you know all this shit?.
快打电话给她  按下"自动拨号一" 那是她的专属代码
Speed dial her. Press "auto one. " That's her button.
-我要说什么? -你为什么不说实话呢?
-What am I supposed to say?. -Why don 't you try the truth?
-你有外遇 -我没有背着凯莉乱搞  我没外遇
- You're cheating. -l' m not cheating on Kelly. I never have.
-你说这又是怎么一回事呢? -听着  你也是男人...
-Then what do you call it? -Look, you' re a guy...
有时候你只想知道 自己还有没有机会
...sometimes you want to know it' s a possibility.
那就像虽然你有个温暖的家
It' s like having a beautiful home...
但你还是梦想着 要去度个小假
...but you still dream of that quick vacation.
住进豪华饭店里 享受着漂亮的风景跟游泳池
You know, some nice hotel room with a great view, maybe a pool.
那只是一个梦想 事实上你根本没有离开家
It's just a fantasy. You never leave home.
-你明白我的意思吗? -凯莉是你的家  潘是汽车旅馆
-Do you hear what I'm saying?. -Kelly is a home and Pam is a motel.
-相信她们知道了一定很感动 -去你的
-I'm sure they'll both appreciate that. -Fuck you.
嘿  你怎么说个不停
Hey, that kind of language is uncalled for.
你不能将这里占为己有 这可是我做生意的地盘
You can't take up the whole booth. This here's my business.
纽约市 不光只有这个电话亭
This is not the only phone in New York.
第八大道上只剩这个电话亭 还能使用
It's the only one on 8th Avenue that's working.
-胡说  到餐厅借电话  快滚开 -混蛋  这是我的电话  快点--
-Bullshit! Go in a restaurant, but get lost. -Motherfucker, this is my phone. Get--
该死  混蛋 你害我伤到手
Goddamn it, man! You done made me hurt my dick hand.
我相信你用另一只手 还是能做生意  快滚开
I'm sure you're just as good with the other hand. Yeah, go away.
我会再回来的  混蛋 我会再回来的  王八蛋  别挡路
I'll be back, motherfucker. I will be back, bitch. Get out of my way!
我很担心你 我还以为她会痛扁你一顿
I was worried for you. I thought she was gonna put an eye out with that hand.
不管你是谁 很明显地你非常聪明
Whoever you are, you're obviously a very intelligent man.
我生活压力很大 我觉得自己快被逼疯了
I know what stress does. It's all I can do from going crazy myself.
-你的意思是我疯了吗? -不  你只是日子不好过
- You're calling me crazy? -No, you're going through a difficult time.
拜托别打电话给我太太
Look, please don't call my wife.
我给你我办公室电话号码 我们好好谈一谈
Let me give you my office number. We'll talk.
我认识一个很不错的摄影师 他可以帮你拍些漂亮的艺术照
I know a reasonable photographer who will do some headshots.
史都  你真的以为 我是演员吗?
Stu, do you really think that I'm an actor?
我不是演员 我不需要你  史都  真的
I'm not an actor. I have no use for you, Stu. None.
我只希望你能告诉凯莉 真正的你是什么样的人
I would just like you to tell Kelly the truth about yourself.
你要打电话给凯莉 告诉她潘的事
So are you going to call Kelly and tell her about Pam?
-还是要我来打呢? -不
-Or do I have to? -No!
天啊  不  我来打
Jesus, no. I'm doing it.
拨号中 凯莉
你很紧张吗?史都
Feeling kind of nervous, Stu?
-喂 -把电话移到话筒旁让我听声音
-Hello. -Hold it to the receiver so I can hear.
-史都 -是我
-Stu?. -Yeah.
-你在哪里? -我在一个电话亭里
-Where are you?. -l' m in a phone booth.
老公  我刚接到一个男人打来的电话 他说你会打电话给我...
Baby, I just got this call from this guy who said you' d be calling me...
你会从电话亭打电话 告诉我一件很重要的事
...from a booth to tell me something important.
有很多人会打恶作剧电话 捉弄别人  亲爱的
There's a lot of prank calling going on today, baby.
-告诉她你邀请女人... -闭嘴
-Tell her you invite women... -Shut up.
到隐密的饭店喝一杯
...to have drinks at discreet hotels.
我不是在跟你说话  老婆
I' m not talking to you, baby.
有人来了
Someone 's got company.
-那个女人是谁? -那混蛋有移动电话
-Who' s that woman?. -Bitch got a cell phone!
-有个妓女想打电话 -他叫我妓女
-Some hooker is trying to use the phone. -He just called me a hooker.
-你确定真的没事? -我们是伴游
-Are you sure there's nothing wrong?. -We are escorts. Escorts.
告诉她你想跟别的女人 上床
Tell her you want to sleep with other women.
有一个人 在散布跟我有关的谣言
There is this person and he's saying things about me.
那些事都不是真的
Things that might not be true.
如果他打给你--快滚开 不然我要报警了
And if he calls you-- Get the fuck out of here before I call the cops!
亲爱的  我想 跟别的女人上床
Honey, I want to sleep with other women.
听着  凯莉  不管他说了什么 别相信他
Look, Kelly, whatever he says, don't believe him.
-我什么都没做 -因为潘要彩排
-I haven't done anything. -Only because Pam had to rehearse.
闭上你的鸟嘴
Shut the fuck up!
史都  我不知道你在说什么 你把我吓坏了
Stu, I don't know what you're talking about, but you're scaring me.
对不起  老婆
I'm sorry, baby.
你能到店里来一趟吗? 我们得面对面地谈一谈
Can you just come over to the store so we can talk in person?.
-我觉得怪怪的 -我会想办法赶过去  别担心
-I feel kind of weird. -Yeah. Look, I'll try. Don't worry.
-少来了 -是啊  王八蛋
-Come on! -Yeah, bitch!
-我也爱你 -"我爱你"
-I love you too. - "I love you. "
快点滚开 不然我要把你们送进监牢里
Get out of here before I have you deported to Jersey.
-你是个天杀的混蛋 -你是个臭婊子
-You're a fucking ass! -And you're a dirty skank.
-你打算怎么办? -你老妈才是臭婊子
-What are you gonna do about it?. -Your mama is a skank, bitch!
你没有跟你太太 说实话  对吧?
You didn't tell your wife the truth, did you, Stu?
你可以感觉得到她真的爱你
And you can tell she really loves you.
有个大美人那么关心你 感觉一定很棒
Must be nice to have a pretty girl care for you.
你为什么要搞砸她的生活? 她从来就没有伤害过你
Why screw up her life?. She never did you harm.
每个人都会造成伤害
Everybody does harm.
够了  这个王八蛋完了
That's it. This mind-fuck is over.
史都  你一挂掉电话 我就会杀了你
Stu, if you hang up, I will kill you.
你手里拿着望远镜 要怎么杀我呢?
What are you going to do about it with your goddamn binoculars?.
我从没说过我拿着望远镜
I never said I had binoculars.
但我能看到 你的超高倍数放大影像
I have a highly magnified telescopic image of you.
什么样的设备 会附有这样的装备呢?
Now what kind of device has a telescopic sight mounted on it?
什么?你拿着来福枪?
What?. You mean like a rifle?.
三十厘米口径  700型 还附有一流的修正器...
A.30-caliber bolt-action 700 with a carbon-one modification...
以及最先进的 韩夏达特军事用望远镜
...and a state-of-the-art Hensholdt tactical scope.
-而它正瞄准了你 -我的头发看起来如何?
-And it's staring straight at you. -Yeah, how' s my fucking hair?.
在这个距离开枪  子弹射出的洞口 大约只有金橘那么大
At this range, the exit wound ought to be about the size of a small tangerine.
你挺高明的  少来这一套
Nice try, pal. Go to hell.
那应该能让你 吓得目瞪口呆吧?
Now, doesn't that just torque your jaws?
我喜欢
I love that.
你知道的  就像在电影里 当好人...
You know, like in the movies just as the good guy...
打算杀掉坏蛋时 他会扣下板机
...is about to kill the bad guy, he cocks his gun.
他为什么不事先扣下板机呢?
Now why didn 't he have it cocked?
因为扣板机的声音太可怕了
Because that sound is scary.
很酷  对吧?
It's cool, isn 't it?
你在这里开枪 一定会引起混乱
Look, you shoot a gun here and there'll be pandemonium.
你听到了吗? 这个地方会挤满了警察
Do you hear me?. There will be cops all over this block.
你如此认为吗? 不妨试试看  一  二
Do you think so? Let's see. One. Two.
没有用的
That won't help you.
三
Three.
史都  你看看每一个人 尖叫声此起彼落
Stu, look at everybody. Look at all of the people screaming, Stu.
警察来了
Here come the cops.
狙击手在屋顶上 枪声大做  打中了电话亭
Sniper on the roof. Gunfire, hit the deck.
史都  你在听我说话吗?
Stu, you still with me?
像个男子汉一样站起来
Stand up and be a man.
你是说你毫无任何理由 只是想把我杀了?
So do you mean you would whack me for no particular reason?.
不  我有很多理由 而且你一直在帮我制造理由
No, I have plenty of reasons, and you keep giving me more.
-你要我杀了他吗? -该死  不要
-Shall I take care of him? -No! No. Shit, no.
那应该很容易
It would be so easy.
拿去
Here.
你刚刚用十块钱打发了那男人
Stu, you just gave that gentleman $ 1 0 to walk away.
你救了他的命 你真是个感性的家伙
You saved his life. You do have a sensitive side.
-你要拿多少钱才会放了我? -就看你有多感性吧
-How much to let me go?. -Let's see how sensitive you really are.
我现在瞄准了你
I'm aiming at you right now.
你感觉到子弹的热力吗?
Can you feel it, the heat of it?
少来了  史都  你可以感觉到
Come now, Stu, you can feel it.
集中注意力
Concentrate.
看看我要射击的地方
Take a look at where I'm going.
你表现得 比其他人好很多
You're doing so much better than the others.
你知道十天前 那个德国色鬼...
You read about the German porn king shot 1 0 days ago...
在三十八街 跟第八街口被杀的事吗?
...at 38th and 8th?
他以为他是个艺术家 不承认他只是一个恋童癖
He thought he was an artist and wouldn 't admit he was just a pedophile.
相信我  他有很多机会 能够逃过一劫
Believe me, he had plenty of chances to come clean.
你一定也知道那个股市经纪人 在四十七街跟第十街口被杀的事
You must have read about the corporate executive shot at 47th and 1 0th.
但你不知道的是 他卖掉他所有的股票
What you didn 't read was that he cashed in all of his stocks...
免得股价崩盘被套牢 但其他的小户却因此失去了一切
...just before the bottom fell out, while all the little guys lost everything.
如果那时他愿意 改过自新...
Now if he had been willing to make amends...
把钱分给大家 结局或许会不一样
...share the money, things might have been different.
请告诉我 我现在瞄准你身上的哪个地方?
Please, tell me, where am I aiming now?
-我的肩膀下面 -哪一边?
-Below the shoulder. - Which one?
右肩
The right shoulder.
-你去死吧  宝贝 -这真是太难得了  史都
-Love to love you too, baby! -That's phenomenal, Stu.
你表现得比其他人好很多
You're doing so much better than the others.
对那些凶杀案还有什么印象吗?
What do you remember about those killings, Stu?
我不知道
I don' t know.
喔  你不是一向自认聪明吗? 猜猜看吧
Well, you think of yourself as a smart guy, Stu. Try.
-他们被射死  我不知道  好吗? -好吧  我给你一个暗示
-They got shot. I don' t know, all right?. -Okay, I'll give you a hint.
皮夹  手表 他们什么东西都没丢
Wallets, watches, everything was left on their bodies.
因为他们没有被抢 他们是遭到了处决
Because they weren't robberies. They were executions.
他们不必遭受那些的
They didn't have to be.
我到底做错了什么事? 为什么是我?
What did I do to deserve this?. Why me?.
如果你一定想知道答案 那么你还没有做好准备
If you have to ask, then you're not ready to know yet.
-就是这里  该死  快点 -天啊  在电话亭里的家伙
-Right here. Shit. Come on. -Jesus. You, in the booth.
-快点 -现在又怎么了?
-Come on. -Now what?.
你知道你让我的生活 有多么痛苦吗?
You got any idea how much pain you' re making in my life?.
-嘿  看着我 -我听到了
-Hey, look at me. -Look, I hear you!
看着我的眼睛 把电话挂断  快走出来
Look me in the eye. Hang up the phone and walk away.
-别那么做 -我有我自己的问题
-Don't do it. -I got my own problems.
我就是你的问题 你知道为什么吗?
I'm your problem. You know why?.
我手下的女孩一直对我大吼 "理昂  他不肯离开电话亭"
My girls keep yapping at me, " Leon, he won't share the phone."
"理昂  他叫我们滚开"
" Leon, he told us to fuck off."
"除非你让他离开那个电话亭 不然我们会逼疯你"
"We're gonna make you nuts unless you make him get off the fucking phone."
-我只想做生意 -我同意  但我不能挂断电话
-I'm trying to run a fucking business. -I sympathize, but I can't get off the call.
不  你不了解我的意思 我手下有一堆女孩
No, you don't understand me. I got the G-string union here.
她们都快把我搞疯了
They're breaking my balls.
我得容忍她们的胡言乱语 但我不会把你放在眼里
I gotta live with their shit, but not yours.
我再好意地跟你说一次 挂掉电话  走出来
So I'm saying this once, nice, all right?. Hang up the phone. Walk away.
-他的确很有礼貌 -他身上带了移动电话
-He did say it nicely. -He got a cell phone up in there too.
-他根本不必打公用电话 -我没办法挂掉电话
-lt ain't even like he need a phone! -I can't get off the call!
闭嘴  你听到了吗? 我真的觉得吵死了
Shut the fuck up! Do you hear that shit?. It's like nails on a chalkboard.
除非我照她们的话做 不然她们是不会闭嘴的
They ain't gonna fucking stop, till I get their way.
-我的头很痛  朋友 -好吧  我会付钱请你走开
-I'm getting a fucking headache, pal. -All right. I'll pay you to go away.
我不要你的钱 我要你挂断电话走出来
I don't want your money. I want you to hang up the phone and get out.
-一百二十块  它都是你的了 -每个人都可以被收买  对吧?
-$ 1 20. It's all yours. -Everybody has their price, right, Stu?
你要付我一百二十块 租下这个烂电话亭吗?
You're gonna give me $ 1 20 to rent the booth the bums piss in?.
-对  我是个大好人 -我觉得他不太对劲
-Yeah, I'm a nice guy. -Something ain't right with him.
你看看那个家伙 满头大汗的样子
Look at that sweat pouring off that son of a bitch.
-我们惹上一个有病的家伙 -或许他得了传染病
-This one sick mother we started with. -It's probably catching too.
-嘿 -他有爱滋病
-Yo. -He's got AlDS.
-你想租下这个电话亭多久? -我不知道
-How long you want to rent the booth?. -lndefinitely.
-你不知道? -没错
-lndefinitely?. -Yes.
我看起来像个混蛋吗? 我得告诉你一件事
Do I look like a asshole?. Let me tell you something.
-给我五百块  我就不会烦你 -等一下  你给我等一下
-$500 gets you indefinitely. -Wait up! Hold the fuck up!
他怎么说服你的? 什么?现在连你都成了大混蛋?
How come he's defying you, huh?. What, you got bitch in you now?.
-我不是叫你闭嘴吗? -你何不用这种语气跟他说话呢?
-Did I say shut the fuck up?. -Yeah, now talk to him like that!
天啊  你喜欢这么做吗?
Jesus Christ. Are you enjoying this?.
-你需要帮助吗? -听着  我可以自己处理
-Do you need help? -Look, I'm handling it.
-少来了 -我可以帮你  史都
-Come on! -I can help you, Stu.
我本来不打算杀你 但你让我改变了心意
I wasn't gonna kill you before, but you changed my fucking mind.
如果我是你  我会乖乖听话的 他会杀了你的
I would take off if I was you. He gonna kick your ass.
-他会杀了你的 -快滚开
-He gonna kick your ass. -Get the fuck out!
请你快点离开 快滚
Can you get out of here?. Will you go away?.
-他好像很生气的样子 -得了吧  我--
-He looks very angry. -Come on. I, look--
-挂掉电话 -叫他离开
-Hang up. -Get rid of him.
-挂掉电话 -我们可以好好谈一谈
-Hang up the phone! -We can work this out!
-叫他离开 -挂掉电话
-Get rid of him! -Hang up the phone.
我有索拉利斯牌的手表 可以卖到两千块
I got a watch. It's a Solaris, $2000 retail.
是吗?我戴的是劳力士金表  混蛋
Yeah?. I got a gold Rolex, motherfucker.
我给你五秒钟的时间 离开那个该死的电话亭  五
You got five seconds to get off the fucking phone. Five.
-他要上了 -四
-Batter up. -Four.
我可以阻止他
I can stop him.
三
Three.
-快说吧  史都 -二  一
-Just say the word, Stu. -Two. One.
不  不要
No, no. Don't. Don't.
该死
Fuck.
我可以为你解决他
This will count as a hang up.
我可以阻止他 只要你开口说好  听到了吗?
I can make him stop. Just say the word. Can you hear me?
-好 -什么?
-Yes. - What?
好
Yes!
-这是谁的地盘? -没错  宝贝
-Whose street is this?. -That' s right, baby.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
宝贝  你在流血吗? 你一定割伤了自己--
Baby, you bleeding?. You must' ve cut yourself--
-怎么回事? -你伤到自己
-What's wrong?. -You cut yourself.
-怎么了? -宝贝  理昂
-What's wrong?. What's wrong?. -Baby?. Leon?. Leon!
-他中枪了 -我的天啊
-He was fucking shot! -Oh, my God!
-混蛋 -他中枪了
-Motherfucker! -He's shot!
理昂
Leon!
快去叫救护车
Somebody call an ambulance!
-打411 -是911才对  笨婊子
-Call 41 1! -91 1, dumb bitch!
他没有呼吸了 快打电话给殡仪馆
He ain't breathing. Call the meat wagon!
-闭上你的鸟嘴 -你开枪杀了他
-Shut the fuck up! -You shot him.
-你为什么要杀他? -你说"好的"
-Why'd you fucking shoot him?. - You said, "Yes. "
"好的  我都听到了" 不等于"好的  杀了他吧"
"Yes, I can hear you," not, "Yes, kill him!"
你说话的时候 应该要小心自己的措词
You ought to be more careful with what you say.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
-混蛋  为什么? -不是我干的
-Motherfucker, why?.! -lt wasn' t me!
-枪在哪里?你看到枪了吗? -去你的
-Where's the gun?. Do you see a gun?. -Fuck you!
你对他开枪  混蛋 我都看到了  他带了枪
You pumped one into him, bitch! I saw it! He's got a Glock!
趴下  大家快趴下 他有枪
Get down! Get the fuck down! Daddy got a Glock!
什么枪?我没有枪 那只是电话
What Glock?. I don't have a fucking Glock! It's a telephone!
你杀了我的男人  混蛋 他们会剥了你的皮  把你分尸
You shot my man, daddy! They gonna skin and fry your ass!
你杀了我的爱人  混蛋 你是个天杀的大混蛋
You shot my baby, daddy! Mr. Motherfucker! Mr. Motherfucker!
拜托  少来了  快进来
Please, come on! Come in here, bitch!
你最好赶快逃命  混蛋
Better run, motherfucker!
警察来了 我希望他们杀了你
The cops is coming and I hope they fry your ass down!
我哪里都去不了  对吧?
I'm not going anywhere, am l?.
如果你对那家伙好一点 我也不会这么做
If you had dealt with the man decently, this might not have been necessary.
我给他钱 还要把我的表送给他
Look, I offered him money. I offered him my watch.
但你不尊重他 那才是他真正想要的东西
But not your respect, which is what he really wanted.
你看不起他 如同那个披萨外送员
You were dismissive like you dismissed the nice pizza guy.
你的罪恶感 来自于你看不起身边的人
You are guilty of inhumanity to your fellow man.
我没有犯任何的错
I' m not guilty of a goddamn thing.
你得为自己做的事负责任 当个男子汉  史都
Take responsibility for what you've done, Stu. Be a man.
这点子真棒 你开枪杀了他  我却要负责任?
I love this fucking spin. You shoot the guy, and I'm fucking responsible?.
喔  你应该好好想一想
Well, looked that way from up here.
我不知道我对你做了什么 但不管我做了什么  我都很高兴
I don't know what I did to you but whatever it was, I'm glad.
我希望自己能够狠一点 我希望你死掉
I wish it had been worse. I wish you died!
-太棒了  你终于愿意说实话 -告诉我你到底是谁
- Yes, finally some honesty. -Just tell me who you are.
我是个你不会注意到的人 我不是你那个世界的人
No one you'd ever notice. I don 't run in your circles.
-你到底是做什么的? -我喜欢观察别人
-And what is it you do?. -I watch.
-你喜欢观察别人? -没错  当你的生活开始走下坡...
-You watch?. - Yes, well, what else is there to do...
你得缩回你的小世界时 你会做些什么事呢?
... when life turns on you and you've retreated into some small room?
你会从窗户往外看
You look out your window.
看到很多人进出这个电话亭 每天都有相同的人来这里打电话
You see people come in and out of this phone booth. The same ones every day.
你会帮他们取名字 想像他们的生活
You make up names for them. You imagine their stories.
但最后你会厌倦于想像 于是开始追逐他们
But eventually, you get tired of imagining and follow one of them.
你听到他说的所有谎言
And you hear all of his lies.
决定他的罪过 应该受到惩罚
And you decide that his sins should be punished.
拿着移动电话大吼大叫的人 无法吸引我的注意力
Some guy shouting into a cell phone full of self-importance isn 't gonna notice me.
但我注意到那个德国色鬼 还有那个黑心的股票经纪人
But I noticed that German porn king, and I noticed that corrupt executive.
我也注意到你  史都
And I noticed you, Stu.
-我真是受宠若惊 -总机553  有什么紧急状况?
-l' m flattered. -Operator 553. What is your emergency?.
请回答
Will you please respond?.
一个在五十三街跟八街口电话亭里
What was so interesting about a guy
打电话的人有什么好稀奇的?
in a phone booth on 53rd and 8th?.
史都秀比电视节目精彩
The Stu Show. Better than TV.
听着  我何德何能 会被拿着来福枪的杀手挑上?
Look, how'd I get so lucky to be picked up by a killer with a rifle?.!
你娶了凯莉 又找潘来偷腥
You had it made. Kelly at home, Pam on the side.
我见过潘一次 我跟踪她到餐厅  她是个大美人
I saw Pam once. I followed her to her restaurant. Lovely.
你过着令人称羡的生活 史都
Life has given you more than your fair share, Stu.
但看来你并不觉得满足
But it appears you don 't appreciate it.
听着  听我说 外表是可以伪装的
Look, look, listen, appearances can be deceiving.
或许我看起来很有自信 事实上我真的很需要别人帮忙
I may look confident, but I'm really, actually just crying out for help!
我需要帮助  你知道吗?
Help! You know?.
我想要帮你  史都 但你不肯帮自己
I'm trying to help you, Stu, but you won't help yourself.
-该死 -怎么了?史都
-Fuck. -What's the matter, Stu?
-你对我开枪 -你应该学乖了  史都
-You shot me! -It's time you learn, Stu.
-欺骗是得不到奖赏的 -欺骗  我欺骗了谁?
-Deception can 't go unrewarded. -Deception! What fucking deception?.
你需要报警 或是叫救护车来吗?
"Are you in need of immediate police or medical response?"
该死  你窃听这个电话亭
Shit. You bugged the fucking booth.
所以你才会知道我的事 你才会知道潘的事
That's how you knew. That's how you knew about Pam.
-你不该跟我说谎的 -听着  我根本没有跟你说谎
- You picked the wrong person to lie to. -Look, I didn' t pick you.
你的时髦西装 吸引了我的注意力
It must have been your flashy suit that attracted me.
我因为身上的衣服被你挑上? 那就是你杀死理昂的原因?
I get fucked on account of my clothes?. That why you killed Leon?.
我杀死理昂 不是因为他穿了什么样的衣服
I didn't kill Leon because of the way he dressed.
那两个家伙也是吗? 他们也穿的很称头吗?
And those other two guys as well?. Did they dress too nice?.
当你走在街上时 你一定觉得自己很高贵
You must feel really expensive when you walk out the door.
太棒了  警察来了
All right, here come the cops.
你打算怎么做?逃跑吗?
What are you gonna do?. Run?.
不  我不是懦夫 我不像我认识的某些人
No, I'm not a coward like some people I know.
-若你现在离开  应可以全身而退 -你把理昂的死怪到我头上
-You can get away if you run now. - You'll blame me for Leon.
不  我会坦诚 我用我的电话杀了他
No, no, l' ll confess I shot him with my fucking phone.
那么我得请你 记住一件事  史都
Well, then I urge you to keep one thing in mind, Stu.
看看你的胸口  你知道 我的枪法有多准多狠
Take a look at your chest. You saw how accurate I can be, how lethal.
现在就杀了我吧 你可以逃之夭夭
Kill me now, and you give yourself away.
没有灭音装置我是逃不了的 那些家伙...
Not with a silencer. It would take these guys...
得花上一整天的时间才能想通 这一枪不是他们的人开的
...the rest of the day to figure out it wasn't one of their own men that did it.
你可能会因为拿出皮夹这个动作 被打成蜂窝
You can be shot 4 1 times for pulling out your wallet.
放下你的武器 双手举高走出来
Throw down your weapon and come out with your hands raised.
-别理他 -是啊  如果他们开枪呢?
-Ignore him. -Yeah, what if they open fire?.
他们不会开枪 看看你的四周  史都
They won 't. Look around you, Stu.
你看到那些 拿着摄影机的观光客了吗?
Do you see the tourists with the video cameras?
他们希望警察 会开枪杀了你...
The ones hoping the cops will blow you away...
那么他们就能销售这卷 最残忍的警匪枪击案录影带?
...so they can sell the tape to The Most Gory Police Shootouts?.
别担心  他们会让警方 保持最完美的形象
Don't worry, they'll keep the police on their best behavior.
只要你不采取敌对的行动 你应该可以平安无事
So long as you don't take hostile action, you should be safe.
平安?你觉得这样很安全吗?
Safe?. You call this safe?.
一整个分局的警察 拿着枪指着我
I got a whole fucking precinct here with guns pointed my way.
双手举高 慢慢地走出电话亭
With both hands raised, moving slowly, step out of the booth.
如果发现你有使用武器的迹象 我们会立刻还击
If we see any signs of a weapon we will respond.
你们不会那么做的  我没有武器
You won't because there isn't any!
把听筒放下 双手高举
Put down the phone and raise your hands!
听着  我办不到 我在讲一通很重要的电话
Look, I can't. I'm on an important call.
请你仔细说明一次
Verify this information for me.
电话亭里的那个人 开枪杀了那边那个家伙...
The guy in the booth shot that guy over there...
他一直待在电话亭里 讲电话
...and stuck around to make a phone call.
对  那个妓女 是那么说的
Yeah, that's what the hookers are saying.
好吧  把扩音器拿来
All right, give me the horn.
-我命令你配合我们的指令 -我很忙  好吗?待会再来吧
-Sir! I'm ordering you to fully comply. -I'm busy, all right. Come back later.
-非常好  史都 -快走出电话亭...
-Very good, Stu. -Step out of the booth...
双手高举 我是在命令你
...and raise your hands. I am giving you an order.
这里由我发号施令  对吧?史都
I give the orders here, Stu, don 't I?
这家伙希望我们 杀了他  队长
This guy is looking for us to kill him, captain.
他想让警察杀了他? 喔  那是不可能的
Suicide by a cop?. Well, that's not gonna happen.
快把尸体搬开
Get that body out of here fast.
派个人去搬开尸体 打电话叫救护车把尸体运走
Somebody get the body. Tell the ambulance to get the body.
每天有好几千人死掉 但你把一具尸体...
Thousands of people die every day, but you put one dead body...
放在繁忙的街道中间 那会逼得大家抓狂
...in the middle of a busy street and it makes people crazy.
看看这些家伙 你可以感觉到他们的恐惧
Look at these guys. You can smell the fear.
-十个警察 -这让我想起了越南
-T en cops. - This reminds me of Nam.
-越南? -没错  越南
-Vietnam?. - Yes, Vietnam.
我那时还太小  无法从军 但我看过照片
I was too young to go, but l' ve seen pictures.
照片无法表达出真相  史都 你无法想像那种恐惧跟压力
Well, pictures can 't do it, Stu. You can 't imagine the fear, the stench.
遭到焚烧的尸体 孩子们把手榴弹丢进你的鞋子里
Napalm-charred bodies, children leaving grenades in your boots.
-你因为参战受到唾弃 -我回家后发现大家都朝我吐口水
-Then you got blamed for the war. -I came home and people spit on me.
对  这个国家 应该跟你道歉
Yeah, this country owes you an apology.
听着  我能够想像你还是个小孩子 从战场中回家的样子...
Look, I just had this vision of you, of a kid, coming back from the war...
你习惯杀人 没办法找到工作  与世隔绝
...inured to the killing, not able to get work, isolated.
我想那会是一个很感人的故事...
I think that could be made into an affecting story...
你知道的 大家会了解这个故事
...and, you know, one that everyone understands.
我想警察 也会站在你那一边
And I think cops are on the side of vets.
你真的很可悲  史都 你为何不清醒一点?
You are pathetic, Stu. Why don't you wake up?
被火焚烧的尸体 打越战时我已经五十岁了
Napalm-charred bodies? I'd have to be 50 to be in that war!
请你不要再误导我了
Stop fucking with my head, please!
我得跟他谈谈
I'm gonna go talk to him.
我们应该等 特警队的谈判高手来
Shouldn't we wait on the ESU negotiator?.
他们二十分钟后才会到 我不想冒那个险
They could take 20 minutes. I'm not gonna take a chance on this one.
我要亲自处理这件事
I'm gonna handle this.
先生  我现在要解除武装
Sir! I'm taking out my weapon.
我会把枪放在车上
Putting my weapon down on the car.
-队长要上了 -我没有武器
-The captain's going in. -I'm not armed.
-是啊  我也没有武器 -我叫做雷米
-Yeah, neither am l. -My name is Ramey.
-爱德华雷米队长 -好吧
-Captain Ed Ramey. -All right.
-你叫什么名字? -我不想跟你做朋友
-What's yours?. -I don't want to be friends.
我不知道 你看起来很需要朋友的帮助
I don't know. It looks like you could use a friend right now.
-告诉他你已经有朋友了 -我已经有朋友了
-Tell him you've already got a friend. -I already got a friend.
你是指那个 跟你在通电话的人吗?
Is that who you're talking to on the phone?.
听着  我只是想听听你的说法 就是那样而已
Look, I just want to hear your side of it. That's all.
我什么都不会说 我也没有开枪杀人
I ain't got no side of it, and I didn't shoot anybody.
你看到我身上有枪了吗? 你看
You see a fucking gun anywhere?. Look.
枪就在你的后裤袋里 我看到了  他....
It's in your back pocket! I see it! He been....
先生  你的口袋里 有武器吗?
Sir, do you have the weapon in your pocket?.
没有  我只有一只移动电话 跟香烟  我没有枪
No. I got a cell phone and I got cigarettes. I got no fucking weapon.
你为什么要在电话亭里 打公用电话?
Then what are you doing in a phone booth making calls?.
-你想看看吗?看吧 -嘿
-You want to see it?. Here. -Hey!
别乱动  大家别开枪
Don't reach for that! Hold your fire!
你不必那么做 我知道里面有什么东西
I don't need to see it. I know what's there.
有很多目击证人 看到你开枪
I got plenty of witnesses over here who saw you use it.
他们什么都没看到 因为我没有开枪
They didn't see it because it didn't happen!
-叫他们闭嘴 -他死了  你说你没有开枪
-Shut them up! -He's dead, but it didn't happen?.
-那么是谁开的枪呢? -别告诉他  史都
-Then who did it?. -Mustn't tell him, Stu.
-我不知道 -你是跟他距离最近的人
-I don't know. -You were the closest one to him.
-你一定看到了整个经过  帮帮我 -不
-You must've saw it happen. Help me. -No.
-这家伙害我觉得很紧张 -听着  你别管这件事
-This guy is getting on my nerves. -Look, stay the fuck out of this.
你到底在跟什么人 通电话?
Who do you keep talking to on the phone?.
-没什么 -你的朋友、父母还是你的爱人?
-Nobody. -Your friend, your parent, your lover?.
-谁? -小心点  史都华
-Who?. -Careful, Stuart. Careful.
我的心理医生
My psychiatrist.
-太棒了  我该想到这一点的 -我懂了  你的医生叫什么名字?
-Excellent. I should've thought of that. -I see. What' s this doctor' s name?.
如果我们知道他是谁 那能帮我们一个大忙
It would be really helpful to us if we knew.
他叫我不要告诉你  好吗? 这是私人的秘密
He says not to tell you, all right?. It's privileged information.
非常好  史都华 看吧  你已经开始上手了
Very good, Stuart. See, now you're having fun.
-是啊  随便你怎么说 -我尊重你的隐私权
-Yeah, whatever you fucking say. -I respect your right to privacy.
我也看过心理医生 那是局里的安排
I've been through therapy myself. The department provided it for me.
我知道当警察的人不应该这么说 但有时候...
I know it's not good form for a cop to be saying that, but sometimes...
你知道的  环境、压力-- 我也有问题  因此赔掉了我的婚姻
...you know, circumstances, stress-- I had issues. I lost my marriage over it.
叫他别再靠近
Tell him not to come any closer.
别再靠近我  快停下来 退后几步
Don't come any closer. Stop there. Go back a few steps.
-退回刚刚的地方 -好的  没问题
-Go back to where you were! -Okay. No problem.
-好了 -你有一些私人问题
-That's right. -So you got some intimacy issues.
我也一样  我只想知道 到底发生了什么事?
I got those too. All I want to know is, what happened, man?.
-叫他念你的权利给你听 -念我的权利给我听
-Tell him to read you your rights. -I want you to read me my rights.
别再问问题
Stop asking questions.
你有权保持沉默 你有权聘请律师
You have the right to remain silent. You have the right to an attorney.
如果你请不起律师 政府会帮你请一个律师
If you cannot afford one, an attorney will be provided for you.
好吗?现在你至少得告诉我 你叫什么名字?
All right?. So now, can you at least give me your first name?.
-只要告诉我你叫什么名字就好 -别告诉他
-Just your first name. -Don't tell him.
我有权不告诉你 我的名字
It' s my right not to have any first name.
-你没有枪  也不说出你的名字 -没错
-No gun, no name. -That's right.
-你非常清楚自己的权利 -叫他把你的律师找来
-You're highly underprivileged. -Demand your lawyer.
把我的律师找来  好吗?
And go get my lawyer too. All right?.
我要请律师到这里来 洽谈我要投降的事
I want an attorney brought down here to negotiate my surrender.
-这一招太聪明了  史都 -我了解  但是...
-Just brilliant, Stu. -I understand that, but...
要请律师冒着生命危险 到这里来真的是很困难
...it' s gonna be difficult to get a lawyer to come and risk his life.
-一旦你把枪交出来-- -我怎么办得到?
-Once you hand over the gun-- -How can l?.
你根本不让我把手 放进我的口袋里
You won't let me put my hand in my pocket?.
我们会帮你把枪拿出来 现在你要做的事...
We'll take it out for you. All you have to do...
就是高举双手乖乖地走出来 你不会有事的
...is step out with your hands raised. Nothing will happen to you.
-这是行不通的 -史都
-It's not gonna work. -Stu, Stu.
-什么? -问他一个问题
-What?. -Ask him a question.
他太太是不是厌倦了 跟他上床呢?
Ask him if his wife got tired of sleeping with him.
-我....该死  我办不到 -你绝对办得到  史都
-l.... Fuck. I can' t do that. -Oh, sure you can, Stu.
问他是不是不举 他是不是无法满足她
Ask him if he couldn 't get it up, if he couldn 't satisfy her.
-你想离开那个电话亭吗? -不行  我办不到
-Are you gonna step out of the booth?. -I can't. No.
-你不想离开那个电话亭吗? -快问他
-You' re not stepping out of the booth?. -Ask him.
-你不愿意吗? -快问他
-ls that a no?. -Ask him!
-这攸关你们两个的性命安全 -先生
-Both your lives depend on it. -Sir?.
队长  你无法满足 你太太的性欲吗?
Captain, you couldn' t satisfy your wife sexually?.
-你说什么? -问他现在会不会自慰?
-Excuse me?. -Ask him if he abuses himself now?
-他会不会在寂寞的夜晚自慰? -去你的  我的天啊
-Does he masturbate on lonely nights? -Fuck. For God's sake!
快问他
Say it!
快问他  不然我要杀了他
Say it or I will blow him away!
-你现在都靠自慰吗? -嘿
-So do you whack off now?. -Hey!
我会去帮你 把律师找来  好吗?
I'm gonna see about that lawyer for you, okay?.
-好的 -放轻松
-Yes. -Just relax.
-史都  我想你伤了他的心 -我要知道是谁在跟他通电话
-Stu, I think you hurt his feelings. -I wanna know who' s on that phone.
找技术人员过来 我要知道那个人到底是谁
I want a techie here. I need to talk to somebody about that phone.
你觉得我们太过份了吗?史都华 我们应该投降吗?
Do you think we went too far, Stuart? Should we give ourselves up?
或许我该请人 来洽谈我投降的事
Maybe I'd like someone to negotiate my surrender.
-我相信我们能解决这件事 -我不把自己的命交给别人处理
-I'm sure we can work that out. -I won't just spill my guts to anyone.
你能让我上全国联播新闻吗? 我是说你的关系很好  对吧?
Could you get me national news? I mean, you've got connections, right?
-没错 -你能请赖利金来吗?
-Sure. -Could you get Larry King down here?
赖利金为什么 要到这里来?
Why the fuck would Larry King come here?.
因为你们是朋友 要不然你还能请谁来呢?
Because you're friends. Who else could you get, huh?
你能请来汤姆布洛克吗? 还是丹莱瑟?黛安莎耶呢?
Could you get Tom Brokaw? How about Dan Rather? Diane Sawyer?
-听着  我不知道  他们很忙 -我不知道  他们很忙
-Look, l, l, I don't know. They're busy. -I, I, I busy.
麦克华伦斯呢?还是泰德卡帕尔? 彼德詹宁斯?凯蒂柯瑞克?
How about Mike Wallace? Ted Koppel? Peter Jennings? Katie Couric?
艾尔洛克?还是任何人? 你谁都请不到
Al Roker? Anybody? No! Nobody.
面对现实吧  你是个无名小卒 你的信用已经破产
Face it, Stu, you're smalltime. And you've got a credibility problem.
你不必担心 我的信用问题  好吗?
Don' t fucking worry about my credibility! All right?.
你又是个有信用的人吗?
What about yours?.
第二频道跟第五频道的人来了 你地方电视台的朋友来了
Look, it's our friends from channels two and five. Your local news, Stuart.
你就没办法帮客户做到这一点 除非是跟你的生命安全有关
You couldn't do this for your clients if your life depended on it.
但我让你扬名四海
But me, I've made you famous.
把你的头伸出去 让他们能够清楚地拍到你
Stick your head out so they can get a better angle on you.
-他们是来报导我的死讯 -你真是不知道感激
-They' re here to cover me dying. -How ungrateful.
那些摄影机会让警察 格外地谨慎
Those cameras will make the police very careful.
-快为他们笑一个 -你可以听到他们的通话内容吗?
-So come on, smile a little for them. -Can you tap into that phone call?.
-那应该不是问题 -但是...
-Should be no problem. -Except...
我们得先拿到许可令 若他真是跟他的心理医生通电话
...we' ll need a warrant if he' s on the line with his shrink.
去你的  我不会因为技术问题 放弃掉这个案子
Fuck that. I' m not gonna jeopardize this on a technicality.
听着  追踪电话来源 应该是不犯法的  对吧?
Look, tracing, that's not a violation, right?.
-只要我们不监听就行了 -好吧  就这么办吧
-As long as we don't listen in. -Okay, this is what I want you to do.
我要你查出来他在跟谁通话 以及对方现在的地址
I want you to find who he's talking to and their current location.
好吗?大家都知道了吗?
All right?. We get that?.
我要找人查出来 到底发生了什么事
I want somebody to find out what's going on.
看看你的对面 你会知道全纽约的人看到了什么
Look across the street and see what everybody in New York is looking at.
你成了大人物  史都华 你成了众人注目的焦点
You're the man, Stuart. You're the center of attention.
这将会成为全国性的新闻 ABC  CBS  CNN  UPN....
Wait till this goes national: ABC, CBS, CNN, UPN....
所有的电视台 都会播出你的新闻  史都
You're gonna hit the whole alphabet, Stu.
再过一个星期大家就会忘了我
I' ll be forgotten about in a week.
没有人会记得 受害者的姓名
No one ever remembers the names of the victims.
反而是凶手可以登上 时代杂志封面  对吧?
It's the killers that get the cover of Time magazine. Right?.
好好想一想  你会成为名人 泰德邦迪  约翰韦恩嘉西...
Think about it. You'd be famous. Ted Bundy, John Wayne Gacy...
还有该死的杰佛瑞达莫 说个受害者的名字  你一定办不到
...fucking Jeffrey Dahmer. Name a victim. You can't.
总之我不配 成为众人注目的焦点
Anyway, I don't deserve to be the center of attention.
-他们要报导的人应该是你 -我不喜欢受人注目
-lt ought to be you they're covering. -That attention would embarrass me.
-我知道他们有多期待报导这件事 -恐惧如何启发你的创意?
-I know exactly the spin to put on this. -How terror inspires your creativity?
听着  这只是媒体的狂热 好吗?你可以请来芭芭拉华特丝...
Listen, this could be a media frenzy, all right?. You'd get Barbara Walters...
你还能请来赖利金 如果你还对他有兴趣
...I mean, Larry King if you still wanted him.
那似乎代表着 我应该放过你  乖乖地投降
That approach seems predicated upon me surrendering without killing you.
听着  我们能帮你争取到同情 还能请来作家帮你写书
Listen, we can make you sympathetic, sit with a writer, bang out a book.
还能帮你拍电影 让所有的美国人支持你
You know, movie of the week. Get America on your side.
好吧  你杀了理昂 因为他想杀我
All right, you killed Leon because he was gonna kill me.
你为了保护我所以杀了理昂 好吗?
You killed Leon to protect me. All right?.
在一个谁都不理谁的城市里 你勇敢地挺身而出
In a city where nobody looks out for anybody, you took a stand.
我是你最好的证人
I'm your best witness.
你要我相信你 可以帮我全身而退?
So you want me to trust you to get me out of this?
没错  我要你相信我 相信我
Yes, I do. I want you to trust me. Trust me.
史都  你一定以为我疯了
Stu, you must think I'm crazy.
-该死  布拉曼来了 -我会应付他
-Oh, shit. Here comes Braman. -l' ll take care of him.
你们应该等我到了之后 再开始跟嫌犯展开接触
Hey. Should' ve waited for me to initiate contact with the suspect.
我已经跟嫌犯说过话 需要你帮忙的话我会告诉你
I established a rapport. Let you know if I need help.
你是想上电视吗?
Are you grandstanding for TV cameras?.
还是你想把这件事 交给专家来办呢?
Or do you want to leave this to a professional?.
在专家还没有到之前 我会亲自处理这件事
Until a professional gets here, I'll handle it.
你是个风趣的家伙  好吧 如果有人因此丧命  你也完了
You're a funny guy. All right, you get somebody else killed, it's on your head.
你懂吗?
Got it?.
我打算这么做  好吗? 城市饭店在这里
This is what I want to do, okay?. This is the City Hotel here.
我要派三个人守在大厅 这里派五个神枪手
I want three guys in the lobby here. And five sharpshooters up here.
想办法派两个神枪手 守在地铁站
See if you can get me two in the subway.
搞什么?
What the fuck?.
-你不打算接电话吗? -不行  我不能碰电话
-Not going to answer it? -I can't. I can't reach for the phone.
-警察会以为我要拔枪 -我敢说一定是凯莉打来的
-The cops will think it's a gun. -I'll bet it's Kelly.
她或许听说了整件事 她一定非常担心你
She's probably heard what you did. She's sick with worry.
我没有办法让她安心 对吧?
I'm not gonna make her feel any better, am l?.
喔  你可以请她 原谅你  史都华
Well, you could ask her to forgive you, Stuart.
你可以坦诚你犯过的错 求她原谅你  让你放下心中的重担
You could confess your sins and beg for absolution, come clean.
你会落到这个地步 就是因为你没有说实话
You're in this position because you're not telling the truth.
我会落到这个地步 因为你手上有枪
I' m in this position because you got a gun!
不  史都华  这是你的罪 你惯于逃避现实跟欺骗
No. Stuart, that is the sin of spin. Avoidance and deception.
我给了你机会改过自新 快告诉她吧
You're being given a chance here to make things right. Now, talk to her.
-听着  我办不到  求求你 -我要你接电话
-Look, I can' t. Please. -I am telling you to answer that phone!
-对不起 -你不能过去
-Excuse me! Excuse me! -You can' t cross in front of here!
快接电话
Answer it!
-听着  我办不到  求求你 -别逼我伤害你
-Look, I can' t. Please. -Don 't make me hurt you!
-跟你太太说话 -那不是她打来的电话
-Talk to your wife! -lt' s not her calling.
-你怎么能那么肯定? -电话是你打来的  你这个混蛋
-How can you be so sure? -lt' s you. It' s you, you miserable fuck!
该死  你逮到我了 你还是能让我对你刮目相看
Damn, you got me! You continue to impress.
你可以开枪杀了我 但你希望动手的人是他们
You could shoot me, but you want them to do it!
-没错  那是个好方法 -是啊
- Yes, well, that's an option. -Yeah.
-队长 -什么事?
-Captain. -Yeah?.
这位女士说那家伙是她丈夫 这是她的身份证
This lady says the perp' s her husband. Here' s her lD.
-我看到新闻时只觉得不可思议 -你觉得他是在跟谁通电话呢?
-I couldn't believe when I saw this. -Who do you think he's talking to?.
我不知道  今天稍早 我跟他通过电话  我告诉他...
I don't know. I spoke to him earlier today and I told him...
-有个男人打电话给我 -有男人打电话给你
-...that there was a man who called me. -A man?.
你跟别的男人说话 让他觉得很生气吗?
Did this upset him, that you were talking to other men?.
对  他的确很生气 但事情不是你想的那样
Yes, he did seem a little upset, but it's, no-- It's not like that.
-我根本不知道那个人是谁 -他的心理医生是谁?
-I didn't even know who this guy was. -Who's his psychiatrist?.
-他没有心理医生 -那只是你看到的那一面
-He doesn't have one. -That you know of.
我认识他三年  跟他结婚一年
I've been with him three years, married for one.
如果他在看心理医生我一定会知道
I'd know if he was in therapy.
我祈祷他最好有在看心理医生 我是离婚后才开始去看心理医生
I wish to God he had been. I saw somebody after my divorce.
他阻止我拿起枪 做出我会遗憾的事
It kept me from picking up a gun, doing something I would regret.
-听我说  史都没有杀人 -女士  在现在的情况下...
-Look, Stu didn't kill anyone. -Ma'am, under the circumstances...
你得好好想想你的丈夫 是不是你认识的那个人
...you need to consider whether your husband is who you thought he was.
因为根据现场目击证人的说法 他有一把枪...
'Cause according to these witnesses over here, he has a gun...
他用那把枪杀人  我们得祈祷 他不会再使用那把枪
...he has used that gun and let's pray to God that he doesn't use it again.
队长
Captain?.
如果你想到他会有什么问题 请你一定要告诉我
If you can think of any dispute he's having currently, please, tell me.
我们撤空了城市饭店 我可以在电话亭附近布置狙击小组
We're clearing City Hotel. I can stage an assault unit within feet of the booth.
还能在电话亭上方 安排狙击手
We've also got sharpshooters securing rooftop positions.
-你们就定位后通知我一声 -没问题
-Let me know when you're in position. -Absolutely.
电话来源追踪得如何了?
What about that wire tap?.
我们正在努力中 你得等上一阵子  好吗?
We're working on it. You gotta hold tight a while, all right?.
-没问题 -好吧
-Yeah, no problem. No problem. -Okay.
薛帕德太太
Mrs. Shepard. Mrs. Shepard.
-他喜欢被叫史都华还是史都? -叫他史都就行了
-Does he like being called Stuart or Stu?. -Stu. Call him Stu.
史都  好吧
Stu. Okay.
请跟我来
Come with me, please.
史都
Stu.
你太太就在我身边
I have your wife with me.
所以你才会知道电话不是她打的 你骗了我
That's how you knew she wasn't calling. You deceived me.
-史都 -她不是我太太
-Stu! -She' s not my wife.
你没事吧?
Are you okay?.
-你愿意跟我说话吗? -跟她说话吧  史都
-Can you just talk to me?. - Yes, talk to her, Stu.
听着  她不是我太太
Look, she' s not my wife!
她是个该死的烂演员 我没办法捧红她  她就一直缠着我
She' s some fucked-up, failed actress I wouldn't handle. She's stalking me!
这不是你自己编的吧? 你是他太太  对吧?
You aren't making this up?. You are his wife, right?.
没错  这里有一张 我们的合照
Yes, here's a photograph of us together.
我不知道他在说什么
I don't know what he's talking about.
史都  好好听你太太说的话
Stu. Listen to your wife.
-她不会害你的 -她不是我太太
-She only wants what's best for you. -She's not my wife!
史都  没有人想伤害你
Stu, nobody wants to hurt you.
-我们只想知道发生了什么事 -是啊  非常好
-We just want to know what happened. -Yeah, very good.
回家去吧  你这个疯婆子 你听到了没?回家去吧
Go home, you fucking lunatic! You hear me?. Go home!
拜托你不要把事情弄得更糟 快出来吧
Please don't make things worse. Just come out.
照他们告诉你的话去做
Just do what they tell you to do.
你太太是个死缠你的疯演员 你说你不认识她
Your wife is a crazy actress stalker and you don't know her.
-你们真是天生一对 -叫她离开这里
-That's an interesting match. -Get her out of here!
-够了  我不想再刺激他 -你疯了吗?
-Enough. I don' t want to agitate this. -You out of your fucking mind?.
-快带她离开这里 -不  我不知道发生了什么事
-Come on, get the woman out of here! -No. I don' t know what' s going on.
他在流血  我们的感情很好 今天早上一切都还很美好
He's bleeding-- We-- We're fine. This morning everything was fine.
你待在这里 待在这里  好吗?
You just stay here. Just stay here, okay?.
-好的 -我想她帮我们踏出了第一步
-Okay. -I think she did some good.
-你有律师的电话吗? -不  我们没有律师
-You got a number of that lawyer?. -No, we don't have a lawyer.
他要我请他的律师来 洽谈他投降的事
He asked for his lawyer to come negotiate his surrender.
-我们从来都不需要律师 -你们现在得请个好律师
-Well, we never needed one. -Well, you need a good one now.
听着  你得帮我忙 待在附近不要走  好吗?
Look, you'll do me best by staying near here. Okay?.
我会让你丈夫活着离开这里
I'm gonna get your husband out alive.
-我不会让你把事情给搞砸 -带薛帕德太太离开这里
-I'm not going to let you fuck this up! -Get Mrs. Shepard out of here.
帮她拿点咖啡 或吃的东西来
You know, get her some coffee or something.
你差一点逼死这个家伙 你得跟他谈好条件
You're gonna lose this guy. You need some kind of redemption.
-你为什么要找心理医生? -快把那个混蛋带开
-What are you seeing a shrink for?. -Get the fuck out of my face!
-别碰我 -我没有退缩
-Don't fucking touch me! -I'm not stepping down!
你没事吧?
You okay?.
我没事
Yeah, I'm fine.
你以为她不知道 她被盯上了吗?
You'd think she didn't know she was being watched.
-什么? -美女们总是心里有数
-What?. -But beautiful women always know.
-你是指凯莉吗? -她们都摆出趾高气扬的样子...
-You talking about Kelly?. -That false indifference, superior air...
那只是她们勾引男人的方法 她们希望别人能注意她们
...it's just a tease. They want eyes on them.
她为什么化妆 做头发  打扮的漂漂亮亮的?
Why does she put on her makeup, do her hair, dress so nicely?
这不是为了 她很少能看到的丈夫
Not for her husband that she hardly ever sees.
不  她希望别人能注意到她 我就注意到她了
No, it's for somebody else to notice. I notice.
你在做什么? 离她远一点  别去烦她
What are you doing?. Stay away from her. Leave her alone.
我要完成她的心愿
I'm giving her what she wants.
我敢说你从来没有像我这样 注意过凯莉
I bet you've never looked at Kelly the way I am right now.
-你休想伤害她 -我真的不敢吗?
-Don't you dare fucking hurt her. -Don't I dare?
伤害她的人 不是我  史都华
I'm not the one who has hurt her, Stuart.
他们不知道我们打算 怎么对付他们  对吧?
What they can't know is what we do to them in our minds. Right?
-你这个大变态 -最完美的犯罪手法
-You sick fuck! -The perfect violation.
-别把她扯进这件事来 -你有多少次...
-Leave her out of this. -How many times...
心里头想着要跟潘 在那间饭店的房间里做爱呢?
...have you had sex with Pam in that hotel bedroom in your head?
凯莉不在后 你真的会想念她吗?
Would you really miss Kelly if she was gone?
够了  我受不了了 我不会再跟你说话
That's it. Not another word. I'm not talking to you.
你选择赌上 其他人的生命
Your choices put other people in jeopardy.
你什么时候才会学到教训?
When are you gonna learn that?
太好笑了  史都华  你好好看清楚
This is funny. Stuart, look uptown.
这些天才还在电信箱边 试着要监听我们的谈话
These geniuses are still at the juncture box trying to tap in.
但我在电话线的两端 装上了加密装置
Only I have installed an encryption device at both ends of the line.
他们根本无法找到我在哪里...
There 's no chance of a trap trace...
他们拼了老命 想把监听设备装上去  那太可悲了
...so now they've gotta try some fancy LoJack instrument. It's really sad.
希望你没有把希望 放在那些笨蛋身上
I hope you weren 't pinning your hopes on those morons.
事实上我是用伪造的号码 用无线传输跟你通话
Truth is, I'm on a wireless A.D. S. with a cloned number.
他们得花上半个小时 才知道是我是从费城发话
It'll take a half an hour to find out I call forwarded through Philadelphia.
我得告诉你一件事 在他们还没有找到我前就会结束
And let me tell you, this will all be over before they can get a dial tone.
我们无法追踪或接听他们的通话 电话线全部缠成一团
We can' t get a trace or break into the line. It' s like a ball of rubber bands.
我就知道这个案子不太对劲 你继续去想办法
I knew there was something weird about this. You keep working on it.
史都  史都华  少来了 你这么做太孩子气了
Stu. Stuart, come on, you're behaving like a child.
你还是不愿意 跟我说话吗?
Still gonna give me the silent treatment?
喂  史都华  别这么做  拜托你 少来了
Hello. Stuart, don 't do this, please. Come on.
我高贵的妈妈以前常这样对我 她总是用这一招来对付我
My sainted mother used to do this. She used to dish this out.
史都华  求求你别这么做
Stuart, please don 't do this.
史都华  你害我想起 我那不快乐的童年
Stuart, you're bringing back my unhappy childhood.
史都华  跟我说话  拜托你 我受不了了  史都  求求你--
Stuart, talk to me! Please, talk to me! I can 't take it! Stu, please--
我是开玩笑的 我的童年非常快乐
I'm kidding. I had a very happy childhood.
又是我们的大美女 我本来不打算要杀她...
Hey, there 's our girl again. I wasn 't planning on killing her...
但我的计划有变
...but plans change.
告诉我 你到底要我做什么
Just tell me what the fuck you want from me.
喂  你还在啊 我还以为我又在自言自语
Hello. There you are. I thought I was talking to myself again.
你有什么心愿我都会帮你完成 说吧
Anything you want. I'll do it. Just tell me.
告诉凯莉你的真面目 还有你的小爱人
Tell Kelly about the real Stu, about your little motel.
-那样子你就会放了我们吗? -有何不可呢?
-And then you' ll let us go?. -Why not?
-凯莉 -这是个好的开始
-Kelly! -That's a start.
-亲爱的 -把她拉回来
-Baby! -Hold her back!
-嘿 -跟我说话
-Hey! -Talk to me!
-抓住她  把她拉回来 -什么事?
-Grab her! Keep her back! -Yes?.
我在听你说
I'm listening.
凯莉  我打电话给一个女人
Kelly, I called some woman.
-每天都打 -每天都打
-Every day. -Every day.
我被这个女人吸引 我打电话给她....
I was attracted to this other woman. And I called her and....
-我想上她 -我想跟她上床
-I wanted to fuck her. -And I wanted to sleep with her.
不  我想上她
No. I wanted to fuck her.
-快说 -我想上她
-Say it. Say it! -And I wanted to fuck her.
-对不起 -不论你做了什么我都不在乎
-l' m sorry. -Whatever you did, I don' t care.
请你快点出来 好吗?
Please, just come out of the booth. Okay?.
那就是我做的好事 对不起
That' s all I did. That' s all I did. I'm sorry.
好吧  我已经照你的话去做 我已经受够了
All right, I've done what you asked. That's it. I've had enough of this.
我还没有玩完
I haven't.
-你说过你会放了我们 -我改变了心意
-You said you'd let us go. -I changed my mind.
你这个大混蛋  你不能这么做 你不能这么对我
You miserable fuck. You can't do this. You can't do this to me.
听着  我照你说的去做 你要我做的事我都做了
Look, I took all your shit. I did everything you fucking asked.
你骗我 我受够了
You lied to me. I'm done with this.
你真的受够了 你想做什么随便你  再见
I've fucking had enough. You can go fuck yourself! Later.
-他挂掉电话了 -或许他们决定要投降了
-He hung up. -Maybe they already got a trace.
特警队
ESU, ESU?.
-我要投降了 -他出来了
-I'm giving myself up! -He's coming out!
-小心 -我要看到你丢掉武器
-Heads up! -I want to see you toss away your weapon!
把武器丢到电话亭外面 待在原地别动
Throw the weapon outside the booth! Stay where you are!
-先缴械 -别伤害他  求求你们
-First, the weapon! -Don't hurt him! Please, don't hurt him!
-我没有枪 -待在原地别动
-There's no fucking gun! -Stay right where you are!
我要你转身  十指交握 放在头后面  好吗?
I want you to turn around. Interlock your fingers behind your head. Okay?.
-求求你把枪给他们 -凯莉  不
-Please give them the gun! -Kelly, no!
退回去  凯莉
Get back! Kelly!
-不要动 -退回去
-Freeze! -Get back! Get back!
-退回去 -好吧
-Get back! -Okay! Okay!
我要接电话
I gotta answer it.
不要动
Freeze! Don't move.
快停火
Hold your fire!
Hold your fire.
-快停火 -拜托你们
-Hold. Hold. -Please.
-去接电话吧 -你在搞什么?
-Go ahead. Answer it. -What the fuck are you doing?.
他要出来了
He's coming out!
快接电话
Answer the phone.
-你这个懦夫 -嗨  史都
-You fucking coward. -Hi, Stu.
你刚刚发了一顿脾气 说了一些气话...
Now, you've had your little tantrum and you said some things in anger...
我愿意忘了这一切
... that I am willing to forget.
带她回车上去 我要她待在车子里
Get her back in the car! I want her in the car.
如果他不是凶手 凶手会是谁呢?
If he's not the shooter, then who the fuck is?.
队长  那通电话 到底是怎么一回事?
Captain, what the fuck is up with the phone calls?.
-我们可以重新来过吗? -你说谎
-So can we start over? -You lied.
除非自己遭到背叛 不然你不会知道被背叛的痛苦
You can't know the pain of betrayal until you've been betrayed.
凶手就在附近的建筑物里 我要你去跟特警队谈谈
Sniper in one of these buildings. I want you to talk to ESU.
我要你找到 躲在建筑物里的凶手
I want you to get one of these guys, this building.
挨家挨户地搜索 直到你找到那家伙为止  好吗?
Start looking up there from window to window till you find the perp. Okay?.
我要你安静 而且迅速地展开行动  好吗?
I want you to do it quickly, and I want you to do it quietly. All right?.
特警队的指挥官在哪里?
Where's the ESU sergeant?.
你说过我们可以离开的
You said we could go.
-你说过你会放了我们 -别激动  史都华
-You said you'd let us go. -Relax, Stuart.
没有人能第一次就做好
Nobody gets it right the first time.
你已经表现的比其他人好了 你会有机会结束这一切
You've done better than others. You will get a chance to end this.
-我只是还没有玩够 -我玩够了
-I'm just not finished yet. -Yeah, well, I am.
-你没有筹码能留下我 -除了对死亡的恐惧吗?
-There' s nothing keeping me. -Besides the fear of death?
我可以低头躲过你的射击 我可以全身而退
I dive out and you've got one shot. I'm gonna be dancing.
-你以为你能打中我吗? -我可以找几个靶子来练习
-You think you can get me?. -I could go for some target practice.
你只要一开枪  他们就能找到你
One shot, they look for you.
你开了第二枪就等于送自己上西天
Second shot, you give yourself away.
动手吧  史都华  挂掉电话
Go on, Stuart, hang up!
把你的生命交给那些 带着自动武器的警察
Trust your fate to friendly men in flak jackets with automatic weapons.
我相信你可以解释 为什么那个家伙会死掉
I'm sure you can patch up that little misunderstanding about the dead body.
-警察无法证明我杀了人 -你有杀人动机
-Cops can' t prove I killed anyone. - You had motive.
-他们找不到凶器 -现场有很多目击证人
-No weapon. -Plenty of loudmouth witnesses.
找不到凶器  他们就无法定我的罪
No gun and I walk.
-你确定? -是的
-Are you sure? -Yes!
是吗?你杀了一个人 忘记自己把枪藏在哪里了?
Yeah? You murder a guy and you forget where you stashed your gun?
你为什么不推开头顶那块天花板 摸摸看呢?
Why don't you lift the plastic ceiling panel and feel around?
找找看吧
Peekaboo!
日光灯旁边放着什么东西呢? 摸摸看  史都
What's up next to the florescent bulb? Check it out, Stu.
警察一看到我伸手去拿东西 他们会对我开枪的
Cops see me reach for something, they'll blow me away.
只有一个方法能知道答案
There's only one way to find out.
那个家伙身上的子弹 是从你的来福枪射击出来的
Look, the slugs in that dead guy, they came from your rifle.
它们根本就不是手枪子弹 我看过很多的警匪片
They're not gonna match a handgun. I've seen enough cop shows.
子弹在撞击后会变成碎片 史都华  那没有什么好比对的
Hollow points fragment on impact, Stuart. There's nothing to match.
-上面没有枪 -你不相信我吗?
-Only there's no gun up there. -Don 't take my word for it.
你自己去看看吧 里面还装满了子弹
See for yourself. There are rounds left in it.
-我根本就不在乎 -少来了  别让我失望
-I totally couldn't give a shit. -Come on. Don't disappoint me.
运用你的想像力  你有机会的话 就会对我开枪  对吧?
Use your imagination. You'd shoot me if you got the chance, wouldn't you?
我会得意的大笑
With a big fucking smile on my face.
那样才对
There's the spirit.
如果我告诉你 我就在戏院的四楼呢?
Now, what if I told you I was just above the theater, four floors up?
你看到粉红色的窗帘了吗?
See the pink curtains?
对了  史都华  就是那里
There you go, Stuart. Yes.
你好
Yoo-hoo!
你为什么要那么做?
Why would you do that?.
因为这么做很好玩 我们现在拉成平手了  史都华
Because it's fun. The odds are even now, Stuart.
那不就是你想要的吗?
Isn 't that what you wanted?
你知道我在哪里 你手上有枪
You know where I am, and you have a gun.
只要你有机会 你会杀了我
If you have it in you, you can take me down.
该死
Fuck!
-他们会在我开枪前杀了我 -或许你说的对
-They' d kill me before I got a shot. -Oh, you're probably right.
事实上我不在那里
I'm not really there anyway.
你只会打坏 别人家的窗帘
You would've just spoiled some nice lady's curtains.
看来有人看到新闻了
Looks like someone watches the news.
-谁? -你的小爱人
-Who?. - The motel.
-我的天啊 -我想她得拍张艺术照
-Oh, God. -I think she could use a new headshot.
-不 -那么就把枪拿下来
-Don' t! -Then take down the gun.
-听着  她跟这件事无关 -她当然跟这件事有关
-Look, this has nothing to do with her! -She has everything to do with this.
你跟她会在这里 因为你打了电话给她
You're here and she's here because you called her.
快把枪拿下来 别逼我伤害潘  史都华
Now, take it down! Don't make me hurt Pam, Stuart.
-把枪拿下来 -大家准备好
-Take down the gun! -Hey, everybody, get ready.
等一下 我们看看他要做什么  好吗?
Hold on, hold on. Let's just see what he does, all right?.
看看他要做什么
Let's see what he's doing.
上面什么东西都没有
There's nothing there.
但凶器上有你的指纹 警察一定会很乐
Nothing but your fingerprints on the finest cop killer money can buy.
快点  史都  让我看看你有多狠
Come on, Stu. Let's see it.
该死  不  我不会把它拿下来的
Fuck, no! It's staying there.
好吧  那么得有人 来取代你
Fine, then someone will have to take your place.
少来了  史都 你是最称职的人选
Come on, Stu, you're in a perfect position.
-你怎么知道? -你得在她们之间做选择
-How do you figure?. - You get to choose between them.
是潘蜜拉还是凯莉?该由我选吗? 她们之中得有人来代替你
Pamela or Kelly? Should I choose? One of them can take your place.
别这么做
Don' t do this!
你得好好地思索你的感觉 我以为你只爱凯莉
You've got to be more in touch with your feelings. I thought you only loved Kelly!
-没错 -但你对她说谎
-It's true! -But you lie to her.
事情很复杂
It's complicated.
那么我会把事情简单化  史都华 我会除掉你的诱惑  我选潘
Then I'll uncomplicate it, Stuart, by removing temptation. I say Pam.
不  听我说  这不是潘的错 这都是我的错
No! Look, this isn't Pam's fault. This is all my fault!
她是无辜的
She's innocent!
滴答滴答 我们没时间了  好吧  就是凯莉了
Ticktock, ticktock. Time's running out. Okay, Kelly, then.
-那是你的决定 -不  求求你
- You decide. -No, please!
少来了  史都 你还不懂游戏规则吗?
Come on, Stu. Don 't you get the game yet?
你是个自私的男人 做好选择  救自己一命
You're a selfish guy. Pick one and save yourself.
金发还是棕发?我们没时间了
Blond or brunette? Time 's running out.
你或她们?凯莉或潘? 凯莉或潘?
You or them? Kelly or Pam? Kelly or Pam?
快一点  史都
Come on, Stu!
快住手
Stop this.
-我再也受不了了 -你在做什么?快站起来
-I can' t take this anymore. -What are you doing? Get up!
-我在找我的戒指  你看-- -站起来  史都华
-I was looking for my ring. Look-- -Get up, Stuart!
像个男子汉一样站起来 你让自己蒙羞了
Stand up and be a man. You're embarrassing yourself.
队长  我懂了  听我说
Captain! I got it. Listen.
狙击手说他看到目标 从口袋拿出一个黑色的小东西
The rifleman reports subject pulled a small, dark object out of his pocket.
好了  这家伙想在全国联播网上 演出自杀好戏
All right. You're looking at a suicide on national fucking TV.
你要我接手吗?
You gonna let me take this over?.
叫大家稍安勿噪 千万别开火
Tell everybody to hold on, to hold their fire.
大家别开火  保持警戒状态
Everybody hold. Stay ready, but hold.
-史都华  你开始惹毛我了 -你不能这么做
-Stuart, you're beginning to annoy me. -You can't do this.
史都 别再拖下去了  也别再找借口
Stu. No more spinning, no more excuses.
你在做什么?听我说 求求你听我说
What' re you doing?. Look, listen. Listen, please listen to me.
别再拖下去了  史都华
No more delays, Stuart.
听着--我跪下来 求你不要杀我
Look-- l' m on my knees begging you not to kill me.
如果你再装出可怜兮兮的样子 我就会杀了你
I will if you keep up this pathetic spectacle.
对不起  是他打来的  他在说话
Excuse me! He's on the phone, talking.
你从那么高的地方 可以杀掉你想杀的人
From up in your high window, you could kill anyone.
-对  我知道  史都华 -好吧  所以....
- Yes, I know that, Stuart. -All right, and....
你可以用你的来福枪 干掉那些警察
You could pick off any of the cops, with your rifle.
闭嘴  快站起来
Shut up and stand up!
听着  你为什么要威胁凯莉?
Look, why threaten Kelly?.
你喜欢她在店里 跟你讲电话的声音
You liked how she sounded on the phone at the store.
求求你别伤害她 别伤害我太太
Please don't hurt her. Don't fucking hurt my wife.
我不一定要开枪杀了你 但你逼得我别无选择
This doesn't have to end with me shooting you. You leave no choice.
-快站起来 -好吧
-Now, get up! -All right.
好吧  你打算怎么办? 告诉我你打算怎么办
Okay, how does this end?. T ell me how this ends.
戏即将落幕
The stage is almost set.
大家都会边吃晚餐 边看你的死亡纪事
People are gonna be eating dinner watching you die.
有人用狙击的方式杀人
We got a sniper situation here.
打到你店里的电话 是怎么一回事?
What about that phone call to your store?.
今天下午我接到一通电话 我还以为那是通恶作剧电话
I got a phone call this afternoon. I think it was a prank call.
他告诉我史都会从电话亭 打电话给我
He told me Stu would be calling me from a phone booth.
追查她的通话记录 要花多少时间?
How long will it take to get a record of her calls?.
如果他也是使用转接电话 情况就跟现在差不多
If he's using that secure line, we won't know more than now.
或许他没有那么做  他也是个人 他跟我们一样会犯错
Say he didn't. Let's assume he's a human, makes mistakes like all of us.
我得查出那个电话号码 我一直都想知道对方是谁
I need to get that number. I've been waiting for that number.
打电话来的是个男人 听起来大概三十几岁
It was a guy. He sounded like mid-30's.
薛帕德太太  你最好待在车里 好吗?
Mrs. Shepard?. It would be safer if you got back in the car, okay?.
-请你回车上去 -谢谢
-Please get back in the car. -Thank you.
我要你把特警队调到百老汇大道 请他们在那里待命
I want you to divert incoming ESU units to Broadway and hold them there.
-你要我疏散人群吗? -好的
-Want me to clear the streets?. -Yeah.
不  我不希望那个枪手 知道我们的行动
No, no, no. I don't want the sniper to be aware of any of our movements.
他已经知道我们布署的位置
He's already got position on us.
别让他发现 我们知道很多事  好吗?
Let's not let him know we know too much, okay?.
-乔纳 -什么事?
-Hey, Jonah. -Yeah.
别抬头
Don't look up.
请神枪手 搜索那些房间
Get me sharpshooters looking at those windows.
-没问题  队员 -我会在这里帮我们争取一点时间
-You got it, captain. -I'm gonna buy us some time here.
好的
All right.
史都  我可以过去 跟你谈一谈吗?
Stu! It's okay if I come out and talk to you for a second?.
-我不知道 -这家伙很寂寞
-I don't know. -This guy is so lonely.
-他真爱说话 -你做了一个恶梦...
-All he wants to do is talk. -You' re walking through a bad dream...
-发现自己一直醒不过来 -他真的在考验我的耐心
-...and you can' t wake up. -Now he 's really testing my patience.
你想醒过来吗?史都
You wanna wake up, Stu?.
我想  但有一些事 我不能告诉你
I wanna, but I got issues I can' t talk about.
-你在跟你的心理医生讲电话吗? -没错  我付他加班费
-That your psychiatrist on the phone?. -Yeah, yeah. I' m paying him overtime.
你的行为真的很勇敢
That was pretty brave what you did.
我是指你对你太太承认那些事
I mean, admitting all that stuff to your wife.
-你觉得如释重负  对吧? -我应该有那种感觉的
-lt was liberating, right?. -Should've been.
如果我可以 对我太太更坦白一点  那么...
Maybe if I could be more honest with my wife then...
我不知道 结局应该会不一样
...I don't know, something would've turned out different.
拜托
Oh, please.
-信任是关键  你相信我吗?史都 -安排这家伙上欧普拉秀吧
-Trust is the key. You trust me, Stu?. -Get this man a seat on Oprah.
我想  但有一些事 我不能告诉你
I wanna, but I got the issues I can't talk about.
对  那些事攸关生死 叫他退后
Yes, lethal issues. Tell him to stay back.
听着  别再靠近
Look, don't come any closer.
嘿  我不想害你 或是让你感到为难
Hey, I don' t wanna cause or make anything harder for you.
潘  雷米  凯莉  街上的人们 这些人的命都掌握在你手中
Pam, Ramey, Kelly, people on the street, you've got lives in your hands.
我说过这是私人谈话 你到底想做什么?
I told you it's a private conversation. What the fuck do you want?.
我想让你知道 电话亭外面是很安全的
I wanna let you know that it's safe outside the booth.
-才怪 -总是"走出电话亭"
-It's not. -lt' s always, "Get out of the booth!"
我喜欢待在这个电话亭里 好吗?这是我的世界
I like it in the fucking booth! All right?. It's my world.
这是我的电话亭 我不会出去的  好吗?
This is my booth, and I'm not coming out. All right?.
-我永远都不会出去 -我们不会逼你出来...
-Never. -We're not gonna force you out...
因为可能会出现 擦枪走火的状况...
...because there could be some miscalculation...
我永远都不会知道 为什么会发生这种事
...and then I would never find out why this happened.
史都  我怕我得做好准备...
Stu, I'm afraid. I'm afraid that I'm gonna be standing by...
我的手下会开枪 射杀某人...
...and my men are gonna shoot some guy...
当我们知道他手拿着什么东西 一旦我们把他的尸体翻过...
...and when we find out what's in his hand, once we turn over his body...
看到他用什么东西 来威胁大家时....
...and we see what he was threatening people with....
我们知道 那只是一本小圣经
We realize that it was just a little black Bible.
-或是一只移动电话 -别逼我  史都
-Or a cell phone. -Don't push me, Stu.
我不会让那种事发生
I'm not gonna let that happen here.
我只是要打一通电话 一通烂电话--
I wanted to make a phone call. One lousy call--
够了  史都
That's enough, Stu.
-那通电话带来坏消息? -那是最可怕的梦魇
-You got some bad news on that call?. -The worst.
我想说你想拔腿就跑
I bet you want to jump off the edge.
-我觉得自己不断地往下坠落 -我要狠狠地教训他
-l' ve been falling ever since. -I'm gonna push him over the edge.
只要你的一句话
Just say the word.
着地的时候到了
It's time to land.
-一着地我就死定了 -我会接住你的
-When you hit bottom, you die. -l' m your safety net.
拜托你  开口求我吧
Oh, please, say the word.
如果我告诉你你想知道的事 你也会死
If I tell you what you wanna know, you' ll die too.
没错
Exactly.
-我要走了 -很好
-l' m going. -Good.
史都  我们打过电话 给你的律师
But, Stu, we put a call out to your lawyer.
你太太给了我们电话号码
Your wife, she gave us the number.
我会请我最得力的手下 去把他找出来  好吗?
And I got my best men working on bringing him down. Okay?.
够了  那个队长死定了
That's it. The captain gets a bullet.
快点离开 你听到我说的话了吗?混蛋
Get out of here! Hear what I said, asshole?.
-快离开这里  快滚 -别再演了  史都
-Get out of here, go on, now! Go! -Enough of this sideshow, Stu.
-你要为你犯的罪受罚 -原来你是个宗教狂
- Your sins have caught up to you. -So this is all some religious thing?.
那是个好理由  宗教狂热份子 杀了迷信流行的公关人员
That explains it. Bible-crazed killer picks on fashion-obsessed PR guy.
-告诉我你想做什么 -每个人都希望...
-Tell me what you want, then. -What everyone wants...
坏蛋们 能受到应有的制裁
...for the bad guy to get what he deserves.
把那把枪拿出来
Go for the gun.
-你要我自杀? -没错
-Kill myself?. - Yes.
那将会是罕见的无私行为
It would be a rare, unselfish act.
-目标做出危险动作 -除非有命令  谁都不准轻举妄动
-We got hostile action. -Nothing is hostile until I say it is.
-听着  我找不到枪 -凯莉  潘  她们死定了
-Look, I can't find it. -Kelly, Pam, bam! Bam!
好吧  我找到它了
All right! Look, I found it. I got it.
-让大家都能够看到它 -警察会杀了我
-Then let's see it. Let everyone see it. -The cops'll kill me.
没错 你终于进入了状况
Yes. You're talking prime-time material now.
-你大费周章只为了看我被杀死? -不
-All this shit just to watch me die?. -No.
我要你做出你该做的事 你想活命的话就得说实话
To get you to do what's right. If you wanna save yourself, confess.
-我已经把一切都告诉凯莉了 -真的吗?
-I already told Kelly everything. -Everything?
不  别再找借口 说些似是而非的话  史都华
No. No more excuses and half-truths, Stuart.
你得对着摄影机 说出你心里的秘密
You look out into those cameras and you bare your soul.
电视似乎能够让人 说出心里最邪恶的意念
TV seems to help bring out the worst in people.
你会表现的很好
You should be fine.
-技术人员有什么进展吗? -还没有
-How' re those techs doing?. Anything?. -No, not yet. Not yet.
我们还没有找到你的律师 史都  但我们很接近了  好吗?
We haven' t found your lawyer yet, Stu. But we' re getting close. Okay?.
史都华  我给你一个机会 找回真正的自己
Stuart, I'm offering you a chance to redeem yourself.
少来了  在你深爱的人面前 跟数百万个陌生人及我的面前...
Come on, humble yourself in front of your loved ones...
好好地坦白吧 不照我的话做你就得死
...and millions of strangers and me. It's do-or-die time.
什么? 你找不到比我更坏的人吗?
What, you couldn' t find anyone worse than me?.
你没找上凶手或是虐待小孩的家伙 你找上一个公关人员...
Not a murderer or a child molester but a publicist...
他对漂亮的女演员 心存遐想
...who has fantasies about pretty little actresses.
把钱花在意大利制的西装 跟干洗费上...
Who spends money on ltalian suits and dry cleaning...
所以人们会认为他是个大人物 他不会花时间对别人好...
...so people think he's important. Who doesn't waste time being nice...
除非那些人对他来说有利用价值 我这么做有罪吗?
...to people who are of no use to him. These are my crimes?.
史都华  我知道你的罪行 告诉他们
Stuart, I know your crimes. Tell them.
我从来不会为别人做事...
I've never done anything for anybody...
除非我可以利用他们 我一直在玩弄...
...who couldn't do something for me. I string along...
一个孩子 我发誓我会付他薪水
...a kid with promises that l' ll pay him money.
我一直耍着他玩 因为他很崇拜我
I keep him around because he looks up to me.
亚当  如果你在看电视 别当公关  你可以有更好的成就
Adam, if you're watching, don't be a publicist. You're too good for it.
我见人说人话  见鬼说鬼话 我欺骗我的朋友
I lie in person and on the phone. I lie to my friends.
我欺骗报社跟杂志社 他们用我的谎言去欺骗更多的人
I lie to newspapers and magazines who sell my lies to more and more people.
我本身就是一个大谎言 我应该去选总统的
I'm just a part of a big cycle of lies. I should be fucking president.
我穿着一身意大利制西装 因为在心里觉得自己是大草包
I wear all this ltalian shit because underneath, I still feel like the Bronx.
我想我需要这些衣服 跟这只手表
I think I need these clothes, and this watch.
这只价值两千块的表是假的 我也是
My $2000 watch is a fake, and so am l.
我蔑视 所有我该珍惜的事
I neglected the things I should've valued most.
我重视这些鸟事
I valued this shit.
我拿掉婚戒打电话给潘 凯莉  她就是潘
I take off my wedding ring to call Pam. Kelly, that's Pam.
-有人拍到潘了吗? -别怪她
-Somebody got a 20 on this Pam?. -Don't blame her.
我从来没跟她提过我已经结婚 如果我真的告诉她...
I never told her if I was married, and if I did...
她会叫我回家
...she would've told me to go home.
凯莉  看到现在的你 我觉得自己很可耻
Kelly, looking at you now, I'm ashamed of myself.
我是说我努力打造这个形象 史都薛帕德是个大混蛋...
I mean, I work so hard on this image, on Stu Shepard, the asshole...
他完全不理会真正的自己 我证明了自己是个无可救药的人
...who refers to himself in third person, that I only proved I should be alone.
我一直装出很伟大的样子 我真的撑不下去了...
I've been dressing up as something I'm not for so long...
我好害怕你不会喜欢 真正的我
...I'm so afraid you won't like what's underneath.
但这就是我 我是个有血有肉  有弱点的人
But here I am. I'm just flesh and blood and weakness.
我真的好爱你
I love you so fucking much.
我会把婚戒拿掉 因为它提醒了我是怎么伤你的心
I take off this ring because it only reminds me of how I've failed you.
我不想失去你
And, I don't wanna give you up.
我想努力做个好人 但现在这一切由不得我选择
I wanna make things better, but it may not be my choice anymore.
你应该去找更棒的男人
You deserve better.
-你不会放我走的 -没错
-You're not gonna let me go. -No.
你从来都没有那么想过 我知道骗子是什么样的嘴脸
You never were. I know a thing about lies.
我也非常清楚 什么是谎言
I know a thing or two about liars as well.
你为什么要坦白?
Then why the confession?
我那么做不是为了你
I didn't do it for you.
-就在那里 -我知道了
-Right there. -Yeah, got that.
队长  打给他太太的电话 时间是两点十七分...
Captain, captain. The call to his wife originated at 2: 1 7...
发话地点是 巴克利饭店的房间
...at a hard line from the old Barkley Hotel.
-查到房号了吗? -604
-You got a room?. -604.
就是街角的第二排窗户 特警队正准备进攻
Second window from the corner. ESU units holding.
叫他们从五十二街进去
Bring them in from 52nd Street.
封锁所有的门窗跟紧急逃生口 还有所有可能的出入口
Cover the windows, doors, fire escape, every goddamn point of exit.
-特警队  请从五十二街进去-- -史都
-ESU, ESU, come in from the 52nd-- -Stu!
-你的律师来了 -门跟紧急逃生口....
-Your lawyer's coming down now! -Doors, fire escapes....
就是现在
Now!
至少你现在 可以安心地死去
At least you'll die with a clean conscience.
不  该死的人是你 仔细听  你可以听到他们的脚步声
No, you' re the one that' s gonna die! Listen, you can hear them now.
他们去抓你了  你知道为什么吗?
They' re coming to get you. Know why?.
-因为我派他们去抓你 -你就是戒不掉说谎的习惯吧?
-Because I sent them! - You can 't stop lying, can you?
我戒不掉说谎的习惯? 他们已经上楼了
I can' t stop lying?. They' re coming up the stairs.
他们要去抓你了 好好看看你的四周
They're coming to get you. Look around.
那个房间每一秒 都在变小
That room's getting smaller every second.
一寸寸地变小  你知道吗?
Inch by inch! You know what?.
它不会比这个该死的电话亭 还要大
It's not gonna be any bigger than this fucking goddamn booth!
-他们已经就定位 -叫他们采取行动
-They're in position, in position. -Get them to move!
-那里面没有人 -那里面没有人?
-There's nobody there. -There's nobody there?.
他们要冲破那扇门 结束你悲惨的一生
They're coming through that fucking door to put you out of your misery.
你只剩几秒而已 你打算怎么办?
You got a couple seconds left. What're you gonna do?.
如果这是真的 我得拖个人垫背  对吧?
If this is true, I have to take someone with me, don't I?
既然凯莉是你生命中最重要的人 那么我就选她
Since Kelly is the most important thing in your life, I'll take her.
选我吧 你要的人是我
Then take me! Take me. This is about me!
你要杀的人是我 选我吧
I'm the fucking one you want! Take me!
你要的人是我  快动手
This is about me! Come on!
杀我吧  你要的人是我
Take me! It's me you want!
我是雷米队长 快回答
This is Captain Ramey. Somebody talk to me.
我们晚了一步 那个疯子知道我们要进攻...
We're too late. The psycho heard us coming...
他用刀子 割喉自尽
...and slashed his throat with a knife.
-他的情况如何? -他奄奄一息  流了很多血
-What' s his condition?. -Critical. He 's lost a lot of blood.
把他送下来 我不希望任何人死在我面前
Get him down here. I don't want nobody dying on me.
好的
All right.
-凯莉  凯莉在哪里? -你太太没事  好吗?
-Kelly, where's Kelly?. -Your wife's fine, all right?.
好了  别急着起来
All right, try not to sit up.
-我被什么东西打中了? -橡皮子弹
-What hit me?. -Rubber bullet.
如果你注定要挨上一枪 最好还是由我们来开枪
Figured if somebody's gonna shoot you, it might as well be us.
谢谢你
Thanks.
-你们抓到他了吗? -你抓到他了
-Did you get him?. -You did.
-我什么都没错 -给自己一点信心
-I didn't do anything. -Give yourself some credit.
你救了自己一命 不是每次的结局都能这么完美
Got yourself out alive. Doesn't always happen that way.
-你没事吧? -我没事
-Are you okay?. -It's okay. I'm okay.
天啊  我好害怕
God. I was so afraid.
我还以为 我再也见不到你了
I thought I wasn't ever gonna see you again.
我也是
Me too.
我们有很多事得谈一谈
We've got things to talk about.
我只想谈 你愿意告诉我的事
I only want to talk about what you want to tell me.
我什么事都愿意告诉你 真的
I want to tell you everything. Everything.
把担架推过来 这边
Get that gurney over here. Get over here.
他死了
We lost him.
-我想站起来 -我来扶你
-I want to stand up. -I got him.
-你做得到吗? -我得看看他的样子
-Sure you can hold on?. -I gotta see him.
-你不会想看的 -不  我想看
-You don't want to see this. -Yes, I do.
-别激动 -我真的想看
-Take it easy. -Yes, I do.
-让我来 -去吧
-Allow me. Allow me. -Go ahead.
你认识他吗?
You recognize him?.
没错  他曾到这里来 送披萨给我...
Yeah. He was down here trying to deliver me a pizza...
就在我接到电话的十分钟前
... 1 0 minutes before I got the call.
我叫他滚开
I told him to fuck off.
现在的人太坏了
That's enough these days.
等一下
Just give it a minute.
我们会开车过去 你会被送上救护车
We'll be driving, and you'll be flying.
悉听尊便
Whatever you say.
我的天啊
What a piece of shit.
这双鞋很不错
Nice shoes.
是意大利制的
Italian.
你挂掉了电话  史都
You hung up, Stu.
我没机会跟你说再见
I didn't get a chance to say goodbye.
我为那个送披萨的感到难过
I feel bad about the pizza guy.
但我不想错过 你跟凯莉团圆的划面
But I couldn't miss seeing you and Kelly reunited.
你不必谢我 从来没有人谢过我
You don't have to thank me. Nobody ever does.
我只希望你好不容易 找回的诚实能维持下去
I just hope your newfound honesty lasts.
如果你没有那么做 我会再打电话给你的
Because it if doesn't, you'll be hearing from me.
这真的是太有趣了
Isn't it funny?
你听到电话铃声 那可能是其他人的电话
You hear a phone ring, and it could be anybody.
但电话铃声一响 你会很自然地去接起它  对吧?
But a ringing phone has to be answered, doesn't it?
对吧?
Doesn't it?
喂
Hello?.